<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-23T01:18:58.624Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-23T01:18:58.624Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.7.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340991</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/should-devtools-teach-the-css-cascade/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T23:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Judis, two days before I mouthed off about using (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity, has a great blog post not only using that format, but advocating that browser DevTools should show us that value by …
The post Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Array Handbook – JS Array Methods Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6098ce302cd0545b5e944d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a collection of elements or items. Arrays store data as elements and retrieve them back when you need them.  The array data structure is widely used in all programming languages that support it. In this handbook, I'll teach you all about arrays in JavaScript. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte for the Experienced React Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340825</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svelte-for-the-experienced-react-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is an accelerated introduction to Svelte from the point of view of someone with solid experience with React. I’ll provide a quick introduction, and then shift focus to things like state management and DOM interoperability, among other things. …
The post Svelte for the Experienced React Dev appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340919</id>
        <link href="https://csshell.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of common CSS mistakes, and how to fix them
From Stefánia Péter. 
Clever idea for a site! Some of them are little mind-twisters that could bite you, and some of them are honing in on best practices that …
The post CSS Hell appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Basics: 10 Helpful Native Web APIs Every New JavaScript Developer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/angular-basics-10-helpful-native-web-apis-every-new-javascript-developer-should-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/angular-basics-10-helpful-native-web-apis-every-new-javascript-developer-should-know"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These JavaScript APIs are need-to-know for any new developer, including our friends who are getting started in Angular.
When you start coding, you often rely on libraries you might not need. Worse, you can sometimes reinvent the wheel by coding a specific function yourself while a native API exists. 
We are in 2021, and modern browsers are becoming more and more powerful. Every single week, new versions are released with new functionalities to make our lives easier. This is why my goal in this article is to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG) From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 21, 2021 (#3448)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33839</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/PyRsedW1lkI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T10:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Microsoft Build Cloud Skills Challenge 2021 (Microsoft Learn) Introducing WebContainers: Run Node.js natively in your browser (Eric Simons) Announcing new file components, MSAL 2 Provider, and SharePoint Framework library in Microsoft Graph Toolkit (MIcrosoft Graph Toolkit Team) New Uno Platform Docs Launched (Uno Platform Team) TechBash 2021 CFP – Two Weeks Left! Submit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3236]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7496</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/USYgUNau3_w/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Simplifying web apps with Static Web Apps – Aaron Powell ASP.NET, registration of a proxy-decorator service in ServiceCollection – Daniel Wertheim Receiving JSON Objects Stream (NDJSON) in ASP.NET Core MVC – Tomasz Pęczek Testing your Domain when Event Sourcing – Derek Comartin Authenticated Encryption in .NET with AES-GCM – Scott Brady ASP.NET Core – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340933</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/learn/css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo look at this mighty SEO flex from Google: Learn CSS! Well deserved — this is great content. Twenty-three chapters taking you through all the fundamentals of CSS with extra content, like relevant podcasts, interactive examples, and even quizzes to …
The post Learn CSS! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular 11 Tutorial: Code a Project from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>60a6b3ab906c5207e3a7f5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/angular-11-tutorial-code-a-project-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T19:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angular is one of the most popular web frameworks. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create an Angular 11 project from scratch. It uses a public API to create a game database website. You will gain a great foundation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Modern C++ by Building an Audio Plugin]]></title>
        <id>60a694ab906c5207e3a7f544</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-modern-cpp-by-building-an-audio-plugin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of C++ courses teach you how to build toy projects with no real-world application. But it can often be more helpful to write programs people would actually use. We just released a 5-hour C++ course that will teach you how to write modern C++ code by building an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with Version Control Using Git]]></title>
        <id>60a4b5c7906c5207e3a7e2bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-started-with-version-control-and-git/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T15:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you'll learn what version control is and how you can contribute to open-source projects using Git.  We'll get through the fundamentals of Git and I'll give you the knowledge that is indispensable for any web developer. What is Git?Git is a version control software which lets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn JavaScript - A Free 7-hour Interactive Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>60a36742906c5207e3a7da6e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-javascript-interactive-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last four months, I have recorded what is probably the most interactive JavaScript course that has ever been created. The reason I have done this is because I often see new coders fall into the same pitfalls again and again when trying to learn JavaScript, with the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340715</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/can-we-create-a-resize-hack-with-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow new developments in CSS, you’ve likely heard of the impending arrival of container queries. We’re going to look at the basics here, but if you’d like another look, check out Una’s “Next Gen CSS: @container” article. …
The post Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fit-content and fit-content()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340897</id>
        <link href="https://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2021/04/fitcontent_and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s some hardcore deep-dive CSS nerdery from PPK. If you can wrap your mind around min-content (the smallest an element can be based on the content it contains) and max-content (the largest the content of an element can push it) …
The post fit-content and fit-content() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools & Tips for Building Apps with an Accessibility-First Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/tools-tips-building-apps-accessibility-first-mindset</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/tools-tips-building-apps-accessibility-first-mindset"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s take a moment to understand what an accessibility-first mindset is and some simple steps developers can take to create accessible apps.
We may celebrate World Accessibility Day on May 20 this year; however, building apps with an accessibility-first mindset is something we should strive to do every day. But what does that mean—accessibility-first mindset? And why should a developer care?
Building Software Should Be Empathetic
Accessibility expert and JetBrains Developer Advocate Rachel Appel says it be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 20, 2021 (#3447)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33837</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/tZCME5zaIbA/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Developing on a M1 Mac with Visual Studio for Mac (Aaron LaBeau) MvvmGen 1.1.0 and the New Special Edition: PURE CODE GENERATION – No Runtime Dependency For Your Project! (Thomas Claudius Huber) The future of Internet Explorer on Windows 10 is in Microsoft Edge (Sean Lyndersay) What’s new in Flutter 2.2 (Chris Sells) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Web Audio API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/understanding-web-audio-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/understanding-web-audio-api"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand more about the Web Audio API, an API that allows us to create and manage sounds in our browser very easily.
Before the release of HTML5, creating applications that were going to use audio was very difficult. The poor support of browser APIs was the main cause, and developers would have to search and use alternatives that weren’t quite conventional or appropriate for the job.
Can you imagine how developers managed to use audio on the web before the creation of the <audio> element for example? Some…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3235]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7494</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/uz-k--3j60k/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Conversation about ready to run – Richard Lander The Mediator Pattern – Gary Woodfine Improve the performance of git on WSL2 – Piotr Stapp The Future of Windows (and other Platforms) Development – Nick Randolph The future of database DevOps – Pramod Sadalage Developing on a M1 Mac with Visual Studio for Mac – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Public Beta of the Notion API dropped! Woot! Here’s their guide. I’ve been a Notion user and fan for a long time, for both personal and professional team use. They even sponsored a few videos around here a …
The post Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Selectors to Style Your Web Page]]></title>
        <id>60a341f5906c5207e3a7da61</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-css-selectors-to-style-webpage/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS selectors are one of the most important parts of CSS. They give you the ability to target HTML elements on your web page that you want to style. Without CSS selectors, you wouldn't be able to style your page to look how you want. Thankfully CSS selectors have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Web3? The Decentralized Internet of the Future Explained]]></title>
        <id>60a42386906c5207e3a7dfe2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T21:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is going through a paradigm shift. Learn the differences between Web2 and Web3, and why many developers and companies are shifting their approach in building apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize for Change in Software Development]]></title>
        <id>60a469ec906c5207e3a7e1b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-optimize-for-change-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you work at Magic Money Corp, which runs on just three lines of JavaScript: let input = { step1: 'collect underpants' } doStuff(input)  profit(input) // $$$!!! Now imagine that something's wrong with doStuff and you need to take it down for maintenance. What happens if you temporarily comment out the second]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-loader-a-different-way-to-work-with-external-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVGs are awesome: they are small, look sharp on any scale, and can be customized without creating a separate file. However, there is something I feel is missing in web standards today: a way to include them as an external …
The post svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Type 3 Font Support in PdfViewer for WPF, WinForms and Xamarin Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/type-3-font-support-pdfviewer-wpf-winforms-xamarin-is-here</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/type-3-font-support-pdfviewer-wpf-winforms-xamarin-is-here"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Telerik PdfViewer now supports Type 3 fonts for WPF, WinForms and Xamarin!
Until now, Type 3 fonts were the missing piece in our font support and were one of the most-demanded features for the Telerik PdfViewer. We are excited to announce that Type 3 fonts are now fully supported out of the box!
The Telerik PdfViewer for WPF, WinForms and Xamarin already supports a wide range of font types, including:
Type 1 fonts: This is the original format created by Adobe. The glyphs are described using a simplified…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Be Building MVPs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/why-you-should-be-building-mvps</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/why-you-should-be-building-mvps"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Website and app development can be a lengthy and costly process. And there’s no guarantee that your users will even love your product after launch … or is there? Here’s how a proof-of-concept MVP (minimum viable product) can work for you.
When designing something new—be it a mobile app, web app, PWA or website—do you ever feel a sense of dread? Like you know there’s something good here, but you’re worried that the client or your boss has bitten off more than they can chew? And that, once launched, the solut…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 19, 2021 (#3446)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33835</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/UKMOS_RLBJc/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links The Visual Studio family welcomes you at Microsoft Build 2021 (Sachin Thakur) Announcing Flutter 2.2 at Google I/O 2021 (Tim Sneath) Visual Studio 2019 version 16.10 Preview 4 Release Notes (Microsoft Docs) What’s new in Android 12 Beta (Dave Burke) Introducing Angular DevTools (Minko Gechev) Conversation about PGO (Richard Lander) The Future of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3234]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7492</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/Rt1WPkRewek/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Conversation about PGO – Richard Lander Building an Event Driven .NET Application: Setting Up MassTransit and RabbitMQ – Paul DeVito Extending the calculator implementation: Creating a Simple Moving Average calculator in C# – Part 3 – Andrew Lock Azure Static Web Apps: Bring Your Own Function (BYOF) – Dennes Torres 5 Ways to Speed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Break into Ethereum, Crypto, and Web3 as a Developer]]></title>
        <id>60a53182906c5207e3a7e588</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/breaking-into-ethereum-crypto-web3-as-a-developer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I've been talking about my move into the Web3, Ethereum, and crypto space since making the switch from a traditional web, mobile, and cloud background. Since making that move, a shocking number of people have reached out to me who are also thinking about doing the same.  It's really]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinned Audio WordPress Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pinned-audio-wordpress-theme/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m afraid I have to start this with a whole backstory, as the journey here is the point, not so much the theme.
A fella wrote to me a while back outlining a situation he was in. His company has …
The post Pinned Audio WordPress Theme appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freelance Development Pricing Guide – Should Freelancers Bill by the Hour?]]></title>
        <id>60a3780f906c5207e3a7db5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-different-ways-to-charge-for-a-website/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you offer your services as a freelance developer, you have a major say in how you price your project.  But how do you go about charging for a website project? "Well, I just bill by the hour and send an invoice every week or month." ...I hear you say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Neon Text With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340420</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-neon-text-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neon text can add a nice, futuristic touch to any website. I’ve always loved the magic of neon signs, and wanted to recreate them using CSS. I thought I’d share some tips on how to do it! In this article, …
The post How to Create Neon Text With CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia O'Dwyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating PDF from HTML in React Demo: Exporting Invoices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/generating-pdf-html-react-demo-exporting-invoices</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/generating-pdf-html-react-demo-exporting-invoices"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll build a sample invoice in our React app using HTML and CSS, then generate a PDF file based on this content. Plus, we’ll control the generated page size exclusively through CSS.
Welcome to the Generating PDF in React blog post series! In Part 1 of this series, “Generating PDF in React: As Easy As 1-2-3,” we covered the basics around generating PDF in React by including a few basic HTML elements and seeing the quickest way we can generate a PDF file from HTML in React.
In today’s blog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 18, 2021 (#3445)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33833</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/mcaHP0EhR10/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Azure Cosmos DB With EF Core on Blazor Server (Jeremy Likness) The 6 Figure Developer Episode 196 – .NET 6 Preview with Rich Lander (John Callaway) Jeremy Likness on Working with Data on .NET – Azure DevOps Podcast Episode 141 (Jeffrey Palermo) Extending the calculator implementation: Creating a Simple Moving Average calculator in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways to Speed up Your End-to-End Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-ways-to-speed-up-your-end-to-end-tests</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-ways-to-speed-up-your-end-to-end-tests"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end tests are an excellent way to deliver high-quality web applications. Unfortunately, these tests tend to be slower than other tests, creating delays in the development process. Here are five tips you can use to keep your tests running efficiently.
Today’s web applications are more complex than ever. The users of your app expect more than just text and images—they also demand more interactivity and a smooth, seamless experience like they would get from a traditional desktop application. Given the a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3233]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7490</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/uqIvTvnFqao/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T06:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Against consistency – Mark Seemann Exploring the Visual Studio Code REST Book extension for native Notebooks – Scott Hanselman Securing OAuth Bearer tokens from multiple Identity Providers in an ASP.NET Core API – Damien Bowden Custom User Message Extension Methods in C# and MVC – Matthew Jones C# serialization with JsonSchema and System.Text.Json – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340716</id>
        <link href="https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Addy Osmani on images in HTML:
The humble <img> element has gained some superpowers over the years. Given how central it is to image optimization on the web, let’s catch up on what it can do and how it can 
…
The post The Humble `img` Element And Core Web Vitals appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Love Letter to HTML & CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339522</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-love-letter-to-html-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see you. In the back there, behind JavaScript and React and PHP and all those “real” programming languages, I see you. And I appreciate you.
The post A Love Letter to HTML & CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Kolodziej</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euismod]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340594</id>
        <link href="https://www.euismod.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T14:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interactive tool for learning grid syntax from Etesam Ansari. In the Learn section, it teaches you some concepts (involving multiple bits of the grid syntax) then gives you a task to complete by filling out the right syntax. I’m …
The post Euismod appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Organize and Modify Existing HTTP and HTTPS Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-organize-and-modify-existing-http-https-requests</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-organize-and-modify-existing-http-https-requests"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this step-by-step tutorial, learn about how to organize and modify existing HTTP and HTTPS requests.
The Requests list in Fiddler Everywhere provides the option to save, modify, execute and share previously composed requests. When you save a request using the Composer, the request is added to a collection in the Requests list.
Requests List

The Requests list is organized in collections. Each collection is a folder on the root level of the Requests list. A collection can contain saved requests and other …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons Not to Write Your JavaScript Data Grid from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-reasons-not-to-write-your-javascript-data-grid-from-scratch</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-reasons-not-to-write-your-javascript-data-grid-from-scratch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data grids (sometimes referred to as data tables) are an essential part of many business applications, and the task to create them can be monumental. Learn about the pitfalls of rolling your own grid, as noted by our engineering teams and the many we have met in the field.
Of the many awesome things JavaScript (React, Angular, Vue... ) developers can create in their apps, most are really enjoyable, some will give you a bit of a headache but also satisfaction in the end, and a handful should be labeled, “Her…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 17, 2021 (#3444)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33831</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/AbIQzNJeGGI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Azure Static Web Apps is production-ready: These are my 5 favorite things (Dave Brock) Yet Another Podcast – Mark Price on C# 9 and .NET 6 (Jesse Liberty) CoreWCF Reached Its First GA Release (Almir Vuk) Rapid XAML Toolkit v0.12 – Now with extra Xamarin.Forms related goodness (Matt Lacey) Async/Await Calls Gotcha with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3232]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7488</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/gLjlR-fPedg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Async/Await Calls Gotcha with the CSharp ? Null Propagator – Rick Strahl Global Exception Handling in ASP.NET Core – Ultimate Guide – Mukesh Murugan Updating FloatingGlucose to .NET 5 – Display Nightscout or Dexcom Glucose Values on the Windows Desktop – Scott Hanselman Using Auth0 with Static Web Apps – Aaron Powell Azurite and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto-Generated Social Media Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340136</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/auto-generated-social-media-images/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T20:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been thinking about social media images again. You know, the images that (can) show up when you share a link in places like Twitter, Facebook, or iMessage. You’re essentially leaving money on the table without them, because they …
The post Auto-Generated Social Media Images appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 14, 2021 (#3443)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33829</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/xK_-crDCPt4/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Project Reunion | Visual Studio Toolbox (Robert Green & Andrew Clinick) Develop production-scale modern web apps quickly with Azure Static Web Apps (Daria Grigoriu) Surface Duo: Foldable SlidingPaneLayout (Cesar Valiente) The Pylance language server has reached stable! (Savannah Ostrowski) Project Reunion 0.5.7 is now available (Andrew Leader) Web & Cloud Development Using The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Features of Angular’s Ivy Language Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/new-features-angular-ivy-language-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/new-features-angular-ivy-language-service"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T13:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a look at what Angular has officially released with Ivy Language Service, from type checking and error detection to platform consistency and codebase diagnosis.
You might have read our introduction to Angular Language Service post, where we gave you a look at experimental Ivy and what it’s promising. Now Angular has officially released Ivy Language Service, and we are going to take a closer look at the incredible features it offers.
What Is Ivy Language Service?
Whenever you use an integrated developme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 13, 2021 (#3442)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33827</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/L-zz-SCd6HU/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T11:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Angular v12 is now available (Mark Techson) Windows Community Toolkit – Release v7.0.2 (Michael Hawker) AngularDart, Flutter, and the web: Spring update (Tim Sneath) My Favorite C# Features – Part 4: Project Structure (Jeffrey T. Fritz) Introducing the brand-new MvvmGen Library – Writing ViewModels for your XAML Applications Has Never Been More Productive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Telerik UI for ASP.NET AJAX R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-ajax-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-ajax-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to share more about our updates to Telerik UI for ASP.NET AJAX in our most recent release.
Hey developer folks, it’s time for another release with new UI components, features and tooling for your ASP.NET AJAX applications. The Telerik R2 2021 release brings new Switch component, multiple Gantt enhancements such as Planned vs Actual, support for multiple templates for custom content rendering, online technical training available for both active trials and license holders and more.
Read the dedi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Kendo UI for Angular with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-angular-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-angular-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for Angular is here.
With this release, we officially cross the 100 UI component threshold while introducing some highly requested features and UI components that are sure to please any Angular developer out there. Without further ado, let’s jump straight into the latest and greatest in Angular with R2 2021.
Kendo UI for Angular Turns 100!

While we normally may measure how old something is by years, with a UI component library I prefer to measure by total number of component…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Kendo UI for jQuery with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-jquery-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-jquery-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for jQuery is here. With this release comes the new TaskBoard, Skeleton and ActionSheet components, along with a ton of new features and improvements across existing components.
It’s May and you know what that means—another huge update from Kendo UI for jQuery. With R2 2021 we have added some pretty nifty new components, including the new TaskBoard component, and other highly requested features, so let’s get right to it and cover what’s new in the jQuery UI components with R2…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WinForms R2 2021: New Callout Control, Color Variations for Office2019 Theme and Content Controls in RichTextEditor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/winforms-r2-2021-new-callout-control-color-variations-office2019-theme-content-controls-richtexteditor</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/winforms-r2-2021-new-callout-control-color-variations-office2019-theme-content-controls-richtexteditor"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second official release of 2021 is here for the Telerik UI for WinForms suite. Enjoy the variety of new controls and improvements coming in R2 2021.
We are thrilled to announce the new Callout control, dark and gray versions of the Office2019 theme, content controls in RadRichTextEditor, Swiss QR barcode, Toast notifications for .NET 5 and much more. Since customer satisfaction has always been our top priority, 70+ customer-requested issues have also been addressed.
Let’s dive into the sea of new featur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Kendo UI for Vue with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-vue-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-vue-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for Vue is here, bringing six new native UI components for Vue, including the Button, Floating Action Button and Upload components.
The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for Vue is here and with it comes a big list of new native UI components for Vue. Let’s dive straight in to see what’s new in Kendo UI for Vue with R2 2021.
New Components
New Component: Button

Every application needs a button at some point—it’s the main way we get users to perform an action in our Vue application…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 12, 2021 (#3441)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33825</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/HZQ2DujgUxo/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T11:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Manage Windows Package Manager with Group Policy (Demitrius Nelon) Supporting VB.NET in .NET 5 | On .NET (Richard Lander, Klaus Loffelmann & Merrie McGaw) Visual Studio 2019 version 16.9 Release Notes – version 16.9.5 new release (Microsoft Docs) Hosting Uno Platform WebAssembly apps on Azure Static Web Apps (Gerard Gallant) Web & Cloud […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 11, 2021 (#3440)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33823</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/Cr1cWwAYepE/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Put a DPAD on that GC! (Maoni Stephens) String Manipulation in C#: Best Practices (Steve Gordon) Rust for Windows Achieves Full Consumption (Call any Windows API) (David Ramel) Visual Studio 2022 64 bits: Elements of history (Patrick Smacchia) Register for Microsoft BUILD 2021 this year! Here’s a SNEAK PEAK of the First MINUTE! […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 10, 2021 (#3439)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33821</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/fJ3DAx2xzL0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links ASP.NET Core 6 and Authentication Servers (Barry Dorrans) How to create the Tic-Tac-Toe game in Blazor WebAssembly in one hour! (David Grace) C# Async Yield Return: IAsyncEnumerable will change your life!!! (Brian Lagunas) Merge Conflict 253: Past, Present, & Future of Ooui (James Montemagno & Frank Kreuger) Intro of DevOps Dojo (Kan Tang) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 7, 2021 (#3438)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33819</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/1KXFcBgAfF8/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Creating beautiful dual-screen Xamarin.Forms apps (Craig Dunn) Announcing Rust for Windows v0.9 (Angela Zhang) Add a README to Your NuGet Package (Christopher Gill) Building Accessible Mobile Apps | The Xamarin Show (James Montemagno & Rachel Kang) Software Engineering Radio Episode 458: Daniel Roth on Blazor (Priyanka Raghavan) Web & Cloud Development Azure Tips […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 5, 2021 (#3437)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33817</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/KIxVRsSxGJI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T11:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Getting Started with Azure Web PubSub Service (Abhijit Jana) Visual Studio Icon Visual Studio 2019 for Mac version 8.9 Release Notes (v8.9.8 Released) (Microsoft Docs) The Rise of Asynchronous Collaboration and What It Means for Development Teams (Drew Falkman & Jay Garcia) How we use Web Components at GitHub (Kristján Oddsson) .NET Foundation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early — when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>