<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-26T01:27:59.326Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-26T01:27:59.326Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.8.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Hack The Box – Valentine]]></title>
        <id>60ac3a2711ffb70827ef6aec</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-calm-and-hack-the-box-valentine/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T22:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough for Hack The Box Valentine machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React-Hook-Form to Build Beautiful Forms with Chakra UI]]></title>
        <id>60a93b0011ffb70827ef5b0d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-hook-form-with-chakra-ui/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T20:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In HTML, it’s the default behavior for forms to redirect to a new page whenever they're submitted. So in order to provide dynamic functionality, React uses a strategy called controlled components. If you have recently gone through a React course, you probably didn't like this part, because there are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Best Practices for New Developers – How to Create Portfolio-Worthy Work]]></title>
        <id>608706aedd38b9088c2c012c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-design-best-practices-for-new-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a beginner developer, it can be difficult to find ways to use your limited knowledge to support yourself. And at the same time, you won't be able to hone your skills if you aren't using them full time.  It's a precarious spot that I remember being in when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340759</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-i-learned-building-a-word-game-app-with-nuxt-on-google-play/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I fell in love with coding the moment I created my first CSS :hover effect. Years later, that initial bite into interactivity on the web led me to a new goal: making a game.
Table of contents
What’s the game 
…
The post What I Learned Building a Word Game App With Nuxt on Google Play appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes. These cruel villains do not even stop at the beautiful world of software development. But although we cannot avoid making mistakes, we can learn to undo them! This post will show the right tools for your daily work with Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sleek and Modern UI Design with Telerik and Kendo UI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/sleek-modern-ui-design-telerik-kendo-ui</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/sleek-modern-ui-design-telerik-kendo-ui"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rise of cross-platform applications, the goal is to write once and deliver everywhere. Learn how Telerik and Kendo UI provides the capability to style controls across various form factors and platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Editor Demo: Add an Editor Component the Easy Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/react-editor-demo-add-editor-component-easy-way</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/react-editor-demo-add-editor-component-easy-way"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich text editors are used in many React applications. Fortunately, you do not have to create one yourself. In this article, you will learn how to easily add a React Rich Text Editor with the help of the KendoReact component library and implement some of its awesome features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 25, 2021 (#3450)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33844</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/IOIRIsp9nyg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links The Journey to Accessible Apps: Screen Readers (Rachel Kang (SHE/HER)) Microsoft Build 2021: All the sessions to watch out for (Zac Bowden) What I’ve learned from 20 years of programming in C# with Joe Albahari with Q&A session (SSW TV) The Road to Observability from System Down to Code (Idan Shatz) From developers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Powerful Websites with Serverless-Driven CMS Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341383</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-powerful-websites-with-serverless-driven-cms-development/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing the right tools to build a website for your organization is essential, but it can be tough to find the right fit. Simple site builders like Wix and Squarespace are easy for marketers to use, but severely limit developers …
The post Creating Powerful Websites with Serverless-Driven CMS Development appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Bouchefra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Reduce Font Loading Impact: CSS Font Descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-font-loading-impact-css-descriptors/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web fonts are often terrible for web performance and none of the font loading strategies are particularly effective to address that. Upcoming font options may finally deliver on the promise of making it easier to align fallback fonts to the final fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3238]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7500</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/-dYCu6S_uS4/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Tennis kata using the State pattern – Mark Seemann Windows v Linux: Compare ASP.NET Core install & hosting – David Grace .NET Basics – Dustin Moris Gorski Secure an Angular SPA and an ASP.NET Core API using Auth0 – Damien Bowden Structured Logging in ASP.NET Core with Serilog – Code Maze How to use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Node Environment Variables with a DotEnv File for Node.js and npm]]></title>
        <id>60abc6d011ffb70827ef630f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-node-environment-variables-with-a-dotenv-file-for-node-js-and-npm/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T00:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Environment variables are variables that are set outside of a program, often through a cloud provider or operating system.  In Node, environment variables are a great way to securely and conveniently configure things that don't change often, like URLs, authentication keys, and passwords. How to Create Environment VariablesEnvironment variables are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Hack The Box – Nibbles]]></title>
        <id>60626dc29618b008528a9589</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keep-calm-and-hack-the-box-nibbles/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T00:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walkthrough for Hack The Box Nibbles machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340808</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-performance/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T22:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making GitHub’s new homepage fast and performant — Tobias Ahlin describes how the scrolling effects are done more performantly thanks to IntersectionObserver and the fact that it avoids the use of methods that trigger reflows, like getBoundingClientRect. Also, 
…
The post Links on Performance appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Small and Sustainable Habits to Get Your First Dev Job]]></title>
        <id>60aaba5911ffb70827ef5ffc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-small-sustainable-habits-to-get-your-first-dev-job/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T21:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving a big goal like transitioning into a new career can be extremely challenging and overwhelming. The amount of information isn't the problem. We have access to more information than we ever have. The problem is knowing how to effectively execute on the information available to us. The more I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use CSS Media Queries to Create Responsive Websites]]></title>
        <id>60ac07ec11ffb70827ef66e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-media-queries-to-create-responsive-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T20:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Media Queries allow you to create responsive websites that look good on all screen sizes, from desktop to mobile. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp channel that will teach you how to create CSS Media Queries. After learning the basics, you will learn how to use media]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Generate a Code Coverage Report with CodeCov and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>60aa161211ffb70827ef5f2c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-generate-code-coverage-report-with-codecov-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software testing is an important part of the software development process. You run tests at different stages of the software development life cycle, and you'll want to make sure that you have good test coverage.  Here are some key reasons for writing software tests:  Testing prevents you from introducing breaking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[proxy-www]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341153</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/justjavac/proxy-www"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like a good trick. What if… a URL was…  a promise… that fetched said URL?
www.codepen.io.then((response) ={
  console.log(response);
});
That’s what @justjavac did with JavaScript Proxys. A clever trick, that. Don’t @ me about the practicality. Trick…
The post proxy-www appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sands of MAUI: Issue #9]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/sands-of-maui-issue-9</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/sands-of-maui-issue-9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:33:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Sands of MAUI—newsletter-style issues dedicated to bringing together the latest .NET MAUI content relevant to developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best No-Code Tools for Developers in 2021]]></title>
        <id>60a5248c906c5207e3a7e54b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-no-code-tools-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T14:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No-code tools let people across the world build different products and applications without writing code.   Before no-code tools, building simple websites or mobile applications took weeks or months and only experienced software developers could do it.  But that's not the case anymore. Now, you can spin up blogs, websites, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340626</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wrangling-control-over-pdfs-with-the-adobe-pdf-embed-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T13:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By our last estimate, there are now more PDFs in the world than atoms in the universe (not verified by outside sources) so chances are, from time to time, you’re going to run into a PDF document or two. Browsers …
The post Wrangling Control Over PDFs with the Adobe PDF Embed API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raymond Camden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Different Approaches of Setting up the Content in RadPdfViewer for ASP.NET AJAX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-different-approaches-setting-up-content-radpdfviewer-aspnet-ajax</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-different-approaches-setting-up-content-radpdfviewer-aspnet-ajax"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We reveal some known and unknown techniques of loading PDF files/content in RadPdfViewer for ASP.NET AJAX, incorporating the UI component in a diverse set of applications and scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container Queries: Use-Cases And Migration Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/css-container-queries-use-cases-migration-strategies/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Container queries bring media queries closer to the target elements themselves and enables them to adapt to virtually any given container or layout. In this article, we’re going to cover CSS container query basics and how to use them today with progressive enhancement or polyfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 24, 2021 (#3449)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33842</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/XK3SX9JJWts/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T11:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Register for Microsoft BUILD 2021 free! And check out the Developer Keynote on Day 2 (Scott Hanselman) Using CodePush in a React Native for Windows application (Matteo Pagani) Who at Microsoft is using WinUI? | One Dev Question (Ana Wishnoff) David Ortinau on Multi-Platform App Development Using .NET MAUI – Azure DevOps Podcast […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3237]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7498</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/bna1hJKkPtU/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software .NET Framework May 2021 Cumulative Update Preview – Tara Overfield Released: Microsoft.Data.SqlClient 2.1.3 & Released: Microsoft.Data.SqlClient 3.0 Preview 3 – David-Engel Information Show dotnet: Investigating Alpine Linux CVEs in .NET container images – Richard Lander Introducing The .NET Coding Pack for VS Code – Getting Started with C# for Beginners – Scott Hanselman Announcing: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340991</id>
        <link href="https://www.stefanjudis.com/blog/should-devtools-teach-the-css-cascade/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T23:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Judis, two days before I mouthed off about using (X, X, X, X) for talking about specificity, has a great blog post not only using that format, but advocating that browser DevTools should show us that value by …
The post Should DevTools teach the CSS cascade? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript Array Handbook – JS Array Methods Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6098ce302cd0545b5e944d0b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-javascript-array-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In programming, an array is a collection of elements or items. Arrays store data as elements and retrieve them back when you need them.  The array data structure is widely used in all programming languages that support it. In this handbook, I'll teach you all about arrays in JavaScript. You'll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte for the Experienced React Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340825</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svelte-for-the-experienced-react-dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is an accelerated introduction to Svelte from the point of view of someone with solid experience with React. I’ll provide a quick introduction, and then shift focus to things like state management and DOM interoperability, among other things. …
The post Svelte for the Experienced React Dev appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340919</id>
        <link href="https://csshell.dev/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collection of common CSS mistakes, and how to fix them
From Stefánia Péter. 
Clever idea for a site! Some of them are little mind-twisters that could bite you, and some of them are honing in on best practices that …
The post CSS Hell appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angular Basics: 10 Helpful Native Web APIs Every New JavaScript Developer Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/angular-basics-10-helpful-native-web-apis-every-new-javascript-developer-should-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/angular-basics-10-helpful-native-web-apis-every-new-javascript-developer-should-know"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T13:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These JavaScript APIs are need-to-know for any new developer, including our friends who are getting started in Angular.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Rich Text Editor (WYSIWYG) From Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/building-wysiwyg-editor-javascript-slatejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s build a rich text, WYSIWYG-editor that supports rich text, images, links and some nuanced features from word processing apps. We will use SlateJS to build the shell of the editor and then add a toolbar and custom configurations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shalabh Vyas)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 21, 2021 (#3448)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33839</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/PyRsedW1lkI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T10:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Microsoft Build Cloud Skills Challenge 2021 (Microsoft Learn) Introducing WebContainers: Run Node.js natively in your browser (Eric Simons) Announcing new file components, MSAL 2 Provider, and SharePoint Framework library in Microsoft Graph Toolkit (MIcrosoft Graph Toolkit Team) New Uno Platform Docs Launched (Uno Platform Team) TechBash 2021 CFP – Two Weeks Left! Submit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3236]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7496</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/USYgUNau3_w/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Simplifying web apps with Static Web Apps – Aaron Powell ASP.NET, registration of a proxy-decorator service in ServiceCollection – Daniel Wertheim Receiving JSON Objects Stream (NDJSON) in ASP.NET Core MVC – Tomasz Pęczek Testing your Domain when Event Sourcing – Derek Comartin Authenticated Encryption in .NET with AES-GCM – Scott Brady ASP.NET Core – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JSON in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340599</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/json-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Neal tweeted a heck of a little CSS trick the other day, putting JSON inside CSS and plucking it out with JavaScript. Valid values for custom properties are quite liberal! So this looks for a CSS rule (e.g. a …
The post JSON in CSS appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn CSS!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340933</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/learn/css/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T21:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ooo look at this mighty SEO flex from Google: Learn CSS! Well deserved — this is great content. Twenty-three chapters taking you through all the fundamentals of CSS with extra content, like relevant podcasts, interactive examples, and even quizzes to …
The post Learn CSS! appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340715</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/can-we-create-a-resize-hack-with-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you follow new developments in CSS, you’ve likely heard of the impending arrival of container queries. We’re going to look at the basics here, but if you’d like another look, check out Una’s “Next Gen CSS: @container” article. …
The post Can We Create a “Resize Hack” With Container Queries? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fit-content and fit-content()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340897</id>
        <link href="https://www.quirksmode.org/blog/archives/2021/04/fitcontent_and.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s some hardcore deep-dive CSS nerdery from PPK. If you can wrap your mind around min-content (the smallest an element can be based on the content it contains) and max-content (the largest the content of an element can push it) …
The post fit-content and fit-content() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Your Skills Online: Smashing Workshops On Front-End And Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/new-online-workshops-front-end-ux/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front-end and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run online workshops for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools & Tips for Building Apps with an Accessibility-First Mindset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/tools-tips-building-apps-accessibility-first-mindset</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/tools-tips-building-apps-accessibility-first-mindset"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s take a moment to understand what an accessibility-first mindset is and some simple steps developers can take to create accessible apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 20, 2021 (#3447)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33837</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/tZCME5zaIbA/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Developing on a M1 Mac with Visual Studio for Mac (Aaron LaBeau) MvvmGen 1.1.0 and the New Special Edition: PURE CODE GENERATION – No Runtime Dependency For Your Project! (Thomas Claudius Huber) The future of Internet Explorer on Windows 10 is in Microsoft Edge (Sean Lyndersay) What’s new in Flutter 2.2 (Chris Sells) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Implement Authentication In Next.js With Auth0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/implement-authentication-nextjs-auth0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step tutorial on adding authentication and authorization to your Next.js apps, with Auth0. We’ll be using a Next.js SDK to connect our application to the Auth0 API and will create the dynamic API route for React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Facundo Giuliani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Web Audio API]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/understanding-web-audio-api</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/understanding-web-audio-api"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T10:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand more about the Web Audio API, an API that allows us to create and manage sounds in our browser very easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3235]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7494</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/uz-k--3j60k/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Conversation about ready to run – Richard Lander The Mediator Pattern – Gary Woodfine Improve the performance of git on WSL2 – Piotr Stapp The Future of Windows (and other Platforms) Development – Nick Randolph The future of database DevOps – Pramod Sadalage Developing on a M1 Mac with Visual Studio for Mac – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notion API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340731</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notion-api/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T23:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Public Beta of the Notion API dropped! Woot! Here’s their guide. I’ve been a Notion user and fan for a long time, for both personal and professional team use. They even sponsored a few videos around here a …
The post Notion API appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340692</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-loader-a-different-way-to-work-with-external-svg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVGs are awesome: they are small, look sharp on any scale, and can be customized without creating a separate file. However, there is something I feel is missing in web standards today: a way to include them as an external …
The post svg-loader: A Different Way to Work With External SVG appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Type 3 Font Support in PdfViewer for WPF, WinForms and Xamarin Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/type-3-font-support-pdfviewer-wpf-winforms-xamarin-is-here</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/type-3-font-support-pdfviewer-wpf-winforms-xamarin-is-here"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Telerik PdfViewer now supports Type 3 fonts for WPF, WinForms and Xamarin!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Be Building MVPs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/why-you-should-be-building-mvps</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/why-you-should-be-building-mvps"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Website and app development can be a lengthy and costly process. And there’s no guarantee that your users will even love your product after launch … or is there? Here’s how a proof-of-concept MVP (minimum viable product) can work for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns: Mega-Dropdown Hover Menus]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-mega-dropdown-hover-menus/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything to keep in mind when designing and building a mega-dropdown, common pitfalls, hover entry/exit delays, trajectory triangle technique and SVG path exit areas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 19, 2021 (#3446)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33835</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/UKMOS_RLBJc/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links The Visual Studio family welcomes you at Microsoft Build 2021 (Sachin Thakur) Announcing Flutter 2.2 at Google I/O 2021 (Tim Sneath) Visual Studio 2019 version 16.10 Preview 4 Release Notes (Microsoft Docs) What’s new in Android 12 Beta (Dave Burke) Introducing Angular DevTools (Minko Gechev) Conversation about PGO (Richard Lander) The Future of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3234]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7492</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/Rt1WPkRewek/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Conversation about PGO – Richard Lander Building an Event Driven .NET Application: Setting Up MassTransit and RabbitMQ – Paul DeVito Extending the calculator implementation: Creating a Simple Moving Average calculator in C# – Part 3 – Andrew Lock Azure Static Web Apps: Bring Your Own Function (BYOF) – Dennes Torres 5 Ways to Speed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinned Audio WordPress Theme]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pinned-audio-wordpress-theme/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T19:14:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m afraid I have to start this with a whole backstory, as the journey here is the point, not so much the theme.
A fella wrote to me a while back outlining a situation he was in. His company has …
The post Pinned Audio WordPress Theme appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating PDF from HTML in React Demo: Exporting Invoices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/generating-pdf-html-react-demo-exporting-invoices</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/generating-pdf-html-react-demo-exporting-invoices"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T13:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we build a sample invoice in our React app using HTML and CSS and then generate a PDF file based on this content. Additionally we control the generated page size exclusively through CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 18, 2021 (#3445)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33833</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/mcaHP0EhR10/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Azure Cosmos DB With EF Core on Blazor Server (Jeremy Likness) The 6 Figure Developer Episode 196 – .NET 6 Preview with Rich Lander (John Callaway) Jeremy Likness on Working with Data on .NET – Azure DevOps Podcast Episode 141 (Jeffrey Palermo) Extending the calculator implementation: Creating a Simple Moving Average calculator in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways to Speed up Your End-to-End Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-ways-to-speed-up-your-end-to-end-tests</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-ways-to-speed-up-your-end-to-end-tests"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end tests are an excellent way to deliver high-quality web applications. Unfortunately, these tests tend to be slower than other tests, creating delays in the development process. Here are five tips you can use to keep your tests running efficiently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create, Edit And Animate SVGs All In One Place With SVGator 3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/create-edit-animate-svg-svgator3/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking a closer look at [SVGator 3.0](https://www.svgator.com/?utm_source=article&utm_medium=smashingmag&utm_campaign=svgator3_smashing), a new major release of the popular SVG application that lets you create, edit and animate SVG files and make the best out of what SVG has to offer — from start to finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 37 With Adam Argyle: What Is VisBug?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-37/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about VisBug. What is it, and how is it different from the array of options already found in Chrome DevTools? Drew McLellan talks to its creator Adam Argyle to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Organize and Modify Existing HTTP and HTTPS Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-organize-and-modify-existing-http-https-requests</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/how-to-organize-and-modify-existing-http-https-requests"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this step-by-step tutorial, learn how to organize and modify existing HTTP and HTTPS requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Improved Our Core Web Vitals (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/core-web-vitals-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s “Page Experience Update” will start rolling out in June. At first, sites that meet Core Web Vitals thresholds will have a minor ranking advantage in mobile search for all browsers. Search is important to any business, and this is the story of how Beau Hartshorne and his team at Instant Domain Search improved their Core Web Vitals scores.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Beau Hartshorne)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons Not to Write Your JavaScript Data Grid from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-reasons-not-to-write-your-javascript-data-grid-from-scratch</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-reasons-not-to-write-your-javascript-data-grid-from-scratch"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data grids (sometimes referred to as data tables) are an essential part of many business applications, and the task to create them can be monumental. LLearn about the pitfalls of rolling your own grid, as noted by our engineering teams and the many we have met in the field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 17, 2021 (#3444)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33831</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/AbIQzNJeGGI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T11:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Azure Static Web Apps is production-ready: These are my 5 favorite things (Dave Brock) Yet Another Podcast – Mark Price on C# 9 and .NET 6 (Jesse Liberty) CoreWCF Reached Its First GA Release (Almir Vuk) Rapid XAML Toolkit v0.12 – Now with extra Xamarin.Forms related goodness (Matt Lacey) Async/Await Calls Gotcha with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 14, 2021 (#3443)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33829</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/xK_-crDCPt4/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T11:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Project Reunion | Visual Studio Toolbox (Robert Green & Andrew Clinick) Develop production-scale modern web apps quickly with Azure Static Web Apps (Daria Grigoriu) Surface Duo: Foldable SlidingPaneLayout (Cesar Valiente) The Pylance language server has reached stable! (Savannah Ostrowski) Project Reunion 0.5.7 is now available (Andrew Leader) Web & Cloud Development Using The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tree-Shaking: A Reference Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/tree-shaking-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tree-shaking” is a must-have performance optimization when bundling JavaScript. In this article, we dive deeper on how exactly it works and how specs and practice intertwine to make bundles leaner and more performant. Plus, you’ll get a tree-shaking checklist to use for your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Features of Angular’s Ivy Language Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/new-features-angular-ivy-language-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/new-features-angular-ivy-language-service"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T13:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a look at what Angular has officially released with Ivy Language Service, from type checking and error detection to platform consistency and codebase diagnosis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 13, 2021 (#3442)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33827</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/L-zz-SCd6HU/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T11:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Angular v12 is now available (Mark Techson) Windows Community Toolkit – Release v7.0.2 (Michael Hawker) AngularDart, Flutter, and the web: Spring update (Tim Sneath) My Favorite C# Features – Part 4: Project Structure (Jeffrey T. Fritz) Introducing the brand-new MvvmGen Library – Writing ViewModels for your XAML Applications Has Never Been More Productive […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Telerik UI for ASP.NET AJAX R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-ajax-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-ajax-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Telerik R2 2021 release brings new Switch component, multiple Gantt enhancements such as Planned vs Actual, support for multiple templates for custom content rendering, online technical training available for both active trials and licenses and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 12, 2021 (#3441)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33825</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/HZQ2DujgUxo/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T11:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Manage Windows Package Manager with Group Policy (Demitrius Nelon) Supporting VB.NET in .NET 5 | On .NET (Richard Lander, Klaus Loffelmann & Merrie McGaw) Visual Studio 2019 version 16.9 Release Notes – version 16.9.5 new release (Microsoft Docs) Hosting Uno Platform WebAssembly apps on Azure Static Web Apps (Gerard Gallant) Web & Cloud […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 11, 2021 (#3440)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33823</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/Cr1cWwAYepE/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Put a DPAD on that GC! (Maoni Stephens) String Manipulation in C#: Best Practices (Steve Gordon) Rust for Windows Achieves Full Consumption (Call any Windows API) (David Ramel) Visual Studio 2022 64 bits: Elements of history (Patrick Smacchia) Register for Microsoft BUILD 2021 this year! Here’s a SNEAK PEAK of the First MINUTE! […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours — but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 10, 2021 (#3439)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33821</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/fJ3DAx2xzL0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links ASP.NET Core 6 and Authentication Servers (Barry Dorrans) How to create the Tic-Tac-Toe game in Blazor WebAssembly in one hour! (David Grace) C# Async Yield Return: IAsyncEnumerable will change your life!!! (Brian Lagunas) Merge Conflict 253: Past, Present, & Future of Ooui (James Montemagno & Frank Kreuger) Intro of DevOps Dojo (Kan Tang) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>