<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-27T01:06:41.889Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-27T01:06:41.889Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom Property Brain Twisters]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342718</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/custom-property-brain-twisters/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T18:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am part of that 82% that got the answer to Lea Verou's quiz wrong. Stephen Shaw posted a similar quiz as well and it's a fun exercise sharpen your CSS chops.
The post Custom Property Brain Twisters appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cancel Pending API Requests to Show Correct Data]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342911</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-cancel-pending-api-requests-to-show-correct-data/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T14:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently had to create a widget in React that fetches data from multiple API endpoints. As the user clicks around, new data is fetched and marshalled into the UI. But it caused some problems.
One problem quickly became evident: …
The post How to Cancel Pending API Requests to Show Correct Data appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgi Nikoloff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 25, 2021 (#3471)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33889</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/_IYdCVI9820/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Windows 11 design principles (Shawn Hickey & Quinn Radich) Building a new, open Microsoft Store on Windows 11 (Giorgio Sardo) Latest Windows 11 features for developers (Windows Dev Center) Top 10 things you can do to make your app great on Windows 11 (Jim Walker & Quinn Radich) Introducing Windows 11 (Panos Panay) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Multi-Author Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/creating-multi-author-blog-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how we can connect different types of content in a Next.js application. With this technique, we can add any kind of one-to-one, one-to-many, or even many-to-many relationship to our projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dom Habersack)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CodeItLive Summer Series: Chat Tech, Ask Questions, Win Prizes!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/codeitlive-summer-series-chat-tech-ask-questions-win-prizes</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/codeitlive-summer-series-chat-tech-ask-questions-win-prizes"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CodeItLive Summer Series: A series of FREE summer events with your favorite frameworks & favorite techies, and you get to chat tech, ask questions and win prizes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run A UX Audit For A Major EdTech Platform (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/ux-audit-edtech-platform-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a case study of how a UX audit affects a UI. It explains how a famous educational platform can be analyzed edX against Jakob Nielsen’s usability guidelines. To get started, Mark Lankmiller shares all of the criteria and metrics he used for his UX audit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mark Lankmilier)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3260]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7546</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/44wwi9QJZaw/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Introducing Windows 11 – Panos Panay What Windows 11 Means for Developers – Kevin Gallo Developing for Android on Windows – Guy Merin .NET Framework June 2021 Cumulative Update Preview – Tara Overfield Microsoft’s Windows 11 launch event: Here’s what we know – Mary Jo Foley Blazor, TypeScript and Static Web Apps – Aaron […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Common React Mistakes You Might Be Making – And How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>60d3ee396e1a1407b6b0b6ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-react-mistakes-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T17:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go over the most common mistakes you might be making in your React code right now, plus how to fix them. If you want to create amazing React applications, it's essential to avoid many common errors along the way. In this article, we'll not only cover how to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use OpenTelemetry to Understand Software Performance]]></title>
        <id>60d4b5e96e1a1407b6b0bac4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-opentelemetry/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want good performance in your application, you need to collect data to figure out where to make improvements. That's where OpenTelemetry comes in. OpenTelemetry offers a single set of APIs and libraries that standardize how you collect and transfer telemetry data. OpenTelemetry provides a specification for instrumentation so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chapter 9: Community]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chapter-9-community/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April of 2009, Yahoo! shut down GeoCities. Practically overnight, the once beloved service had its signup page replaced with a vague message announcing its closure.
We have decided to discontinue the process of allowing new customers to sign up 
…
The post Chapter 9: Community appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Hoffmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise Of Design Thinking As A Problem Solving Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-thinking-problem-solving-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic and unpredictable environments in which we work, even the most carefully crafted solutions can have a short shelf life. When we accept that our work is impermanent and our problem-solving abilities are limited, our goal can shift from delivering full solutions to developing tools that empower our users to adaptively design for themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Singer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 24, 2021 (#3470)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33887</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/-0zdsqk6z8Q/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T11:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Microsoft needs to show Windows 11 is more than just Windows 10.5 (Tom Warren) Microsoft’s Windows 11 launch event: What to expect and how to watch (Mary Jo Foley) Announcing the launch of Collectives™ on Stack Overflow (Teresa Dietrich) Introducing the new GitHub Issues (Mario Rodriguez) Web & Cloud Development Azure Tips & […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik Reporting and Report Server R2 2021 Service Pack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-reporting-report-server-r2-2021-service-pack</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-reporting-report-server-r2-2021-service-pack"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T10:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The R2 2021 service pack release of Telerik Reporting and Telerik Report Server comes with new features, fixes and improvements. Let’s see what’s in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3259]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7544</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/-_j7BhQRto0/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information What’s new in Windows Forms in .NET 6.0 Preview 5 – Igor Velikorossov NuGet Package Explorer is now a Web App powered by Uno Platform – Uno Team ICYMI C# 9 New Features: More Pattern Matching Features – Jason Roberts Monsters Weekly 213 – Local Testing with Azure Static Web Apps & Monsters Weekly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Data Analysis? How to Visualize Data with Python, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib &amp; Seaborn Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>605abca5687d62084bf6b7cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/exploratory-data-analysis-with-numpy-pandas-matplotlib-seaborn/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data Analysis is the process of exploring, investigating, and gathering insights from data using statistical measures and visualizations.  The objective of data analysis is to develop an understanding of data by uncovering trends, relationships, and patterns. Data analysis is both a science and an art. On the one hand it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices Architecture – Explained in Plain English]]></title>
        <id>6072ffd4d5756f080ba98b27</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/microservices-architecture-for-humans/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last few years, microservices have gone from an overhyped buzzword to something you should understand as a software engineer.  According to an O'Reilly developer survey in 2020:  61% of companies have been using microservices in the last year29% say at least half of their company systems are built]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=343076</id>
        <link href="https://www.bram.us/2021/06/21/tablesng-improvements-to-table-rendering-in-chromium/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T21:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I blogged “Making Tables With Sticky Header and Footers Got a Bit Easier” recently, I mentioned that the “stickiness” improvement was just one of the features that got better for <table>s in Chrome as part of the TablesNG upgrade…
The post TablesNG — Improvements to table rendering in Chromium appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik UI for Blazor 2.25.0—Wizard, Stepper, StackLayout, GridLayout and More!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-blazor-2-25-0-wizard-stepper-stacklayout-gridlayout-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-blazor-2-25-0-wizard-stepper-stacklayout-gridlayout-more"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s release time again and this month Telerik UI for Blazor brings four brand new components—Wizard, Stepper, StackLayout and GridLayout—new features to existing Blazor components such as the Scheduler resource grouping, grouping in drop-down components, plus multiple Grid and TreeList enhancements that are almost a tradition for every new Telerik UI for Blazor version!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342750</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-performant-next-gen-images-in-css-with-image-set/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS image-set() function has been supported in Chromium-based browsers since 2012 and in Safari since version 6. Support recently landed in Firefox 88. Let’s dive in and see what we can and can’t do today with image-set().…
The post Using Performant Next-Gen Images in CSS with image-set appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a REST API with .NET 5 and  C#]]></title>
        <id>60d36eb66e1a1407b6b0b16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-rest-api-with-dot-net-5-and-c-sharp/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET is a popular software framework developed by Microsoft. We just released a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create a REST API end-to-end from scratch using the latest .NET 5 innovations and Visual Studio Code. The course uses the C# programming language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Great Technical Course]]></title>
        <id>60a406bd906c5207e3a7dfcb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-great-technical-course/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you will learn how to create a great technical video course. I run the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel where we post technical courses from a variety of contributors. Video courses that follow the guidelines in this article are often a good fit for freeCodeCamp's channel. How to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Weak declaration”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342669</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/weak-declaration/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PPK looks at aspect-ratio, a CSS property for layout that, for the most part, does exactly what you would think it does. It’s getting more interesting as it’s behind a flag in Firefox and Safari now, so we’ll have …
The post “Weak declaration” appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Online Workshops (July-October 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/new-smashing-online-workshops-frontend-ux-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend and design are remarkably complex these days. That’s why we invite kind, smart folks from the community to run [online workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) for all of us to learn together. And we have new ones coming up, and we’d like to kindly welcome you to join in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Iris Lješnjanin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in R2 2021 SP for Telerik UI for WPF and Telerik UI for WinUI 0.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-r2-2021-sp-telerik-ui-wpf-and-telerik-ui-winui-030</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-r2-2021-sp-telerik-ui-wpf-and-telerik-ui-winui-030"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T12:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest release is now live! It brings over 70 improvements for Telerik UI for WPF as well as the latest .NET 6 preview support! On the Telerik UI for WinUI side, we are adding few brand new components—DateTime Pickers, LookingList and SegmentedControl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 23, 2021 (#3469)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33885</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/7RiMXZhnGyA/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T11:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links NuGet Package Explorer is now a Web App powered by Uno Platform (Uno Platform Team) Package Validation (Anirudh Agnihotry) Blazor on WPF (Sam Basu) Join us for a Live event on Azure Static Web Apps 30th June 2021 (Lee Stott) Web & Cloud Development HTTP Range Requests and Partial Responses With ASP.NET Core […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Words by Our Customers: HORIZON’s Conversion to Telerik Reporting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/words-our-customers-horizon-conversion-telerik-reporting</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/words-our-customers-horizon-conversion-telerik-reporting"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T10:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s take a look at how HORIZON converted to using Telerik Reporting for all their report-writing needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik UI for WinForms R2 2021 Service Pack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-winforms-r2-2021-service-pack</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-winforms-r2-2021-service-pack"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New features and improvements for Telerik UI for WinForms in R2 2021 Service Pack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating Screen Reader Testing On macOS Using Auto VO]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/automating-screen-reader-testing-macos-autovo/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automated testing is an important part of any software project, including testing for accessibility. There are already tools for linting and integration testing accessibility, but what about end-to-end testing with real assistive technology? Since I hadn’t seen this before, I set out to build Auto VO, a driver for the VoiceOver screen reader.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cameron Cundiff)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3258]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7542</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/t11v3Nt9fak/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Package Validation – Anirudh Agnihotry ML.NET June Updates – Bri Achtman Blazor on WPF – Sam Basu Debug & Analyze Dump Files in Visual Studio – Mark Downie RDCMan v2.8, AccessChk v6.14, Process Monitor v3.83, Strings v2.54, Sysmon v13.22 and TCPView v4.13 – Alex Mihaiuc The State of WebAssembly 2021 – Colin Eberhardt 5 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logical Fallacies – Definition and Fallacy Examples]]></title>
        <id>607f5fafdd38b9088c2bd0c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/logical-fallacies-definition-fallacy-examples/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're debating someone, you want to use all the resources at your disposal to convince them you're right. And that's great – but you should be careful that you don't end up using a logical fallacy to help you make your point. What is a Logical Fallacy?A logical fallacy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[inherit, initial, unset, revert]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342930</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/inherit-initial-unset-revert/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are four keywords that are valid values for any CSS property (see the title). Of those, day to day, I’d say I see the inherit used the most. Perhaps because it’s been around the longest (I think?) but also …
The post inherit, initial, unset, revert appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping with PHP – How to Crawl Web Pages Using Open Source Tools]]></title>
        <id>60d2323d6e1a1407b6b0ac4f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-php-crawl-web-pages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T21:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you collect data from web pages across the internet. It's also called web crawling or web data extraction.  PHP is a widely used back-end scripting language for creating dynamic websites and web applications. And you can implement a web scraper using plain PHP code.  But since we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Async/Await to Write Better JavaScript Code]]></title>
        <id>60cac8ff4dc1a607ed7b4592</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-async-await-write-better-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a special syntax you can use in JavaScript that makes working with promises easier. It's called “async/await", and it’s surprisingly straightforward to understand and use.  In this article, we'll discuss:  What are asynchronus functions? How promises work in JavaScript Async/Await basics How to use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeScript and MongoDB to Build a 100 Days of Code Discord Bot]]></title>
        <id>60c13e71d3126007592d5be2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-100-days-of-code-bot-for-discord-using-typescript-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 100 Days of Code challenge is very popular among new coders and developers looking to level up their skills. It's so popular that our Discord server has an entire channel dedicated to it.  By popular demand, we recently built a Discord bot that helps people track their progress in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Custom Elements in Svelte]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342634</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-custom-elements-in-svelte/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte fully supports custom elements (e.g. <my-component>) without any custom configuration or wrapper components and has a perfect score on Custom Elements Everywhere. However, there are still a few quirks you need to watch out for, especially around …
The post Using Custom Elements in Svelte appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Rich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342925</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/if-were-gonna-criticize-utility-class-frameworks-lets-be-fair-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not here to raise a shield protecting CSS utility frameworks. I don’t even particularly like the approach, myself, and nothing is above fair criticism. But fair is a key word there. I can’t tell you how many times I’ve …
The post If we’re gonna criticize utility-class frameworks, let’s be fair about it appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blazor on WPF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-wpf</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/blazor-wpf"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T13:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of promise in bringing Blazor goodness to WPF desktop apps. This would be a wonderful way to modernize WPF apps and share code better between web/desktop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 22, 2021 (#3468)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33883</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/U7MOp5ZmbTU/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T11:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Let’s Learn .NET – Blazor – Free Live Stream Event (James Montemagno) The 6 Figure Developer Episode 201 – Sustainable OSS with Rockford Lhotka (John Callaway) Debug & Analyze Dump Files in Visual Studio (Mark Downie) Charlie Kindel on Terminal.Gui – Azure DevOps Podcast Episode 146 (Jeffrey Palermo) Solitaire in Blazor Part 3 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Development Best Practices That Will Help You Craft Better Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-development-best-practices-help-craft-better-tests</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/5-development-best-practices-help-craft-better-tests"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T10:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automating tests is hard. You can make it manageable by using these tips, techniques and
tools to help you speed up the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing With Code: A Modern Approach To Design (Development Challenges)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/design-code-modern-approach-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of innovation in both tools and processes, the struggle between design and development is still real. This article focuses on the best practices for improving the design to development processes and how cutting-edge solutions, such as UXPin powered by Merge technology, can help in facilitating the change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikołaj Dobrucki)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3257]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7540</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/l0IYs8A1XlM/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Solitaire in Blazor Part 3 – Drawing, Discarding, and the Stacks – Matthew Jones Locked Files When Publishing .NET Core Apps to IIS with WebDeploy – Rick Strahl The cost of the cloud – Oren Eini Microsoft SQL Server Database Security, Disaster Recovery & High Availability – Nikhil Thakkar Introduction to .NET MAUI Blazor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342887</id>
        <link href="https://web.dev/new-responsive/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T21:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Una is calling it the new responsive. A nod to the era we were most certainly in, the era of responsive design. Where responsive design was fluid grids, flexible media, and media queries, the new responsive is those things …
The post Are we in a new era of web design? What do we call it? appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sands of MAUI: Issue #13]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/sands-maui-issue-13</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/sands-maui-issue-13"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Sands of MAUI—newsletter-style issues dedicated to bringing together the latest .NET MAUI content relevant to developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342448</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-css-charts-with-interesting-shapes-glyphs-and-emoji/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s forego the usual circles and bars we typically see used in charts for more eccentric shapes. With online presentations more and more common today, a quick way to spruce up your web slides and make them stand out is …
The post How to Create CSS Charts With Interesting Shapes, Glyphs and Emoji appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image To Text Conversion With React And Tesseract.js (OCR)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-text-conversion-react-tesseract-js-ocr/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have to process data manually because it is served through images or scanned documents? An image-to-text conversion makes it possible to extract text from images to automate the processing of texts on images, videos, and scanned documents. In this article, we look at how to convert an image to text with React and Tesseract.js(OCR), preprocess images, and deal with the limitations of Tesseract (OCR).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ayobami Ogundiran)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 21, 2021 (#3467)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33881</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/2KaqY1Qxm58/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T11:38:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links ASP.NET Core updates in .NET 6 Preview 5 (Daniel Roth) Conversation about networking and Announcing .NET 6 Preview 5 (Richard Lander) Window Manager preview for Xamarin (Craig Dunn) Getting Started with Project Reunion (Windows UI) and Visual Studio 2022 (Nick Randolph) Developer Perspectives Episode 6 | Jessica Engstrom and Alvin Ashcraft (Jessica Engstrom […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Web Designers Can Do to Create Lightweight and Faster Mobile UIs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/what-web-designers-can-do-create-lightweight-faster-mobile-ui</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/what-web-designers-can-do-create-lightweight-faster-mobile-ui"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T10:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google now ranks websites based on how good the mobile experience is. We’re going to look at some design strategies used to make websites extremely fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3256]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7538</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/-dasDqMU8f4/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Type less, code more with IntelliCode completions – Mark Wilson-Thomas C# Pattern Matching Quick Guide And Examples – Khalid Abuhakmeh What to Expect in .NET 6 – Vitalis Ogbonna Caching Enum.ToString to improve performance – Gérald Barré Getting started with Machine Learning and .NET Notebooks – Ryan Palmer ECMAScript proposal: Ergonomic brand checks for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341511</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-the-outline-property-as-a-collapsable-border/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T20:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outline property in CSS draws a line around the outside of an element. This is quite similar to the border property, the main exception being that outline isn’t a part of the box model. It is often used for …
The post Using the `outline` Property as a Collapsable Border appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carter Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Alternative Voice UI To Voice Assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/alternative-voice-ui-voice-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice assistants are currently the most popular use case for voice user interfaces. However, due to the bad feedback loop resulting from voice assistants can only solve simple user tasks such as setting an alarm or playing music. In order for voice user interfaces to really break through, feedback to the user must be visual, not auditive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ottomatias Peura)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Wave of MAUI Controls by Telerik]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-in-telerik-ui-for-maui</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-in-telerik-ui-for-maui"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T14:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Telerik UI for MAUI—Checkbox and Segmented controls; support for WinUI; updated Demo App; new Demo App for WinUI for MAUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342326</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography-2/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I studied the fonts of the top 1000 websites. Here’s what I learned. — Michael Li brings the data. San-serif has total dominance. “[…] it is rare to go below 10px or above 24px.” And poor <h5> always being the 
…
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Editing and Creating Appointments in Telerik Scheduler for Blazor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/editing-creating-appointments-telerik-scheduler-blazor</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/editing-creating-appointments-telerik-scheduler-blazor"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Telerik Scheduler provides all the hooks you need to manage what happens when the user creates, edits or deletes a scheduled event. Or you can take the easy way out and do nothing at all if you’re happy with the Scheduler’s default UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Client-Side Routing In Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/client-side-routing-next-js/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js has a file-based routing system in which each page automatically becomes a route based on its file name. This article will guide you through almost everything you need to know about Routing in Next.js and point you in the direction of related topics and concepts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adebiyi Adedotun)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the IndicatorView in Xamarin Forms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/using-indicatorview-xamarin-forms</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/using-indicatorview-xamarin-forms"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T11:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IndicatorView teams up with CarouselView to let users know which slide of a carousel they’re on. Today let’s learn how to use this tool!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=341948</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/perfect-tooltips-with-css-clipping-and-masking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clipping and masking have been around for a while now in CSS and even have pretty decent browser support. I recently worked on a project that needed to use a clipping technique for tooltips showing above links in text.
Those …
The post Perfect Tooltips With CSS Clipping and Masking appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Hoebregts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=342257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/start-serving-optimized-images-in-vue/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have become extremely important to the effectiveness of websites. They speak a 1000 words, attract attention, and stimulate emotions.
However, web performance is also a growing problem for most websites. And images are at the heart of many web …
The post Start Serving Optimized Images in Vue appeared first on CSS-Tricks. You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn These New Features Introduced in JavaScript ES2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/learn-new-features-introduced-javascript-es2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/learn-new-features-introduced-javascript-es2021"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T12:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post covers the features introduced in ES2021 and also the history of JavaScript and ECMAScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fiddler Team Spotlight: Q&A With Our Manager of Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/fiddler-team-spotlight-manager-software-engineering</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/fiddler-team-spotlight-manager-software-engineering"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A software engineer, QA analyst and security expert walks into a bar. What do you want to learn from this one person?” Get to know a big personality behind the Fiddler family of products in this lively Q&A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Image Is Probably Not Decorative]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/img-alt-attribute-alternate-description-decorative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image placement on the modern web is highly intentional, helping to communicate the overall purpose of a page or view. This means that nearly every image you declare needs to have an alternate description.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 16, 2021 (#3466)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33879</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/5NUH1R8kjG4/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T11:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links dotnet repl (Scott Hanselman) Improving contrast in Microsoft Edge DevTools: A bugfix case study (Patrick Brosset) Measuring the carbon impact of web browsing (Pierre Lagarde) Walking Through Windows 11 (Brad Sams) Conversation about diagnostics (Richard Lander) Migration of Bing’s Workflow Engine to .NET 5 (Ben Watson) Exciting news for Windows Developers: The #ProjectReunion […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Accessibility Tooling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/complete-guide-accessibility-tooling/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new short series of posts, we highlight some of the useful tools and techniques for developers and designers. Recently we’ve covered HTML Emails and SVG Generators. This time we look into different kinds of tools to help you streamline your accessibility testing process. Don’t miss the next one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nic Chan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 15, 2021 (#3465)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33877</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/VGv36l6pPu0/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T11:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links .NET Conf – Focus on F# – Save the Date (July 29, 2021) (.NET Team) Improving Platform Channel Performance in Flutter (Aaron Clarke) 5 ideas for summer reading (Bill Gates) Solitaire in Blazor Part 2 – The C# Classes (Matthew Jones) Uno Platform 3.8 – New WinUI Calendar, Grid controls, 2x performance, new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Up Multiple WordPress Sites Locally With DevKinsta]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/multiple-wordpress-sites-locally-devkinsta/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing themes and plugins for WordPress, we need to test them in different environments. How can we create multiple testing sites on our computer, quickly and easily, without having to become a sysadmin?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 39 With Addy Osmani: Image Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-39/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of the Smashing Podcast, we’re talking about image optimization. What steps should we follow for performant images in 2021? We talk to expert Addy Osmani to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 14, 2021 (#3464)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33873</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/dEKBBd9EnGw/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links The Future of Web Development with .NET and Blazor (Daniel Roth) Startup Performance, Skia and the Future of Cross Platform Apps Built with .NET and Optimising Startup Time for Cross Platform Apps (Nick Randolph) Learn What’s New in .NET Productivity (Mika Dumont) Xbox & Bethesda Games Showcase Recap and Diablo II: Resurrected Is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When CSS Isn’t Enough: JavaScript Requirements For Accessible Components]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/css-javascript-requirements-accessible-components/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler alert: tooltips, modals, tabs, carousels, and dropdown menus are some of the user interface components that require more than CSS. To ensure accessibility of your interface, JavaScript is a necessary addition to accomplish focus management, respond to keyboard events, and toggle ARIA attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Making Use Of Audio]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/web-design-done-well-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design often revolves around visuals, but the other senses deserve love too. In this article, we tune in to audio features that are making sites sing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 11, 2021 (#3463)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33871</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/FQ0AmoJa4bI/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T11:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Ready to sponsor TechBash 2021? Check out our prospectus! (TechBash Team) Satya Nadella and Phil Spencer reveal what’s next for gaming and its importance to Microsoft (Athima Chansanchai) Registration now open for Microsoft Inspire 2021 (Rodney Clark) Remote Repositories extension for Visual Studio Code (Brigit Murtaugh & Eric Amodio) Web & Cloud Development […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Front-End Boilerplates And Starter Kits]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/useful-frontend-boilerplates-starter-kits/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t need to write everything from scratch every single time. With boilerplates and starter kits, we can set up our projects faster, and get to work immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Front-End Auditing Tools I Discovered Recently]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/three-frontend-auditing-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a faster website can be a rocket task these days. There are so many things to consider, so it’s challenging to get everything right. Here are some less-known tools that might help you get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Judis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 10, 2021 (#3462)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33869</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/r-aEOzY0h6A/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T10:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Bringing Visio to Microsoft 365: Diagramming for everyone (Seth Patton) Azure static web apps CLI, building apps locally (Chris Noring) .NET Rocks! – Event Sourcing with Jeremy Miller (Carl Franklin & Richard Campbell) Build more accessible Angular apps (Emma Twersky) Low Ceremony, High Value: A Tour of Minimal APIs in .NET 6 (Dave […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 9, 2021 (#3461)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33867</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/r35Yz8m53pk/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T11:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Build apps for Microsoft Teams with .NET (John Miller) Uno Platform isn’t a Card Game – Adventures in .NET 072 (Shawn Clabough & Wai Liu) DEVintersection Keynote: The Future of Modern Application Development with .NET and Azure (Scott Hunter) Must-have JetBrains Rider Plugins For ASP.NET Core Developers (Khalid Abuhakmeh) Conversation about containers (Richard […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet <code>:has</code>, A Native CSS Parent Selector (And More)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/has-native-css-parent-selector/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes relational selector one of the most requested features and how are we, as developers, working around not having it? In this article, we’re going to check the early spec of the :has selector, and see how it should improve the CSS workflow once it’s released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From AVIF to WebP: A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/image-optimization-book-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s here! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our deep-dive guide to understand how to deliver high-quality images on the web fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – June 8, 2021 (#3460)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33865</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/AMl8tMwBzW4/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T11:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Developer Nation Survey is now open! Answer questions about your favorite tools and platforms for developers and no-code software creators, make an impact on the future trends, and win prizes. (Developer Economics) dotNET Dev Show: An Update on WinUI 3.0 with Alvin Ashcraft (Sam Basu) Data Validation with the Microsoft MVVM Toolkit (Diederik […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Geocoding App In Vue.js Using Mapbox]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/building-geocoding-app-vue-mapbox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll be taking a general look at the concepts of forward geocoding and reverse geocoding, and will build a mini-app that applies these concepts to display specific locations, using Mapbox and Vue.js 2.6.11 to achieve this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Prince Chukwudire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Webpack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/getting-started-webpack/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern browsers provide good support for JavaScript modules, but module bundlers such as webpack stay a critical part of the JavaScript toolchain. Let’s take a deep dive into what webpack is and how to use it in your development workflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Shared State In Vue 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/managing-shared-state-vue3/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing large-scale Vue applications can be a challenge. In this article, Shawn Wildermuth dives into the pros and cons of approaches like factories, shared objects, and using Vuex. He also explains what is coming in Vuex 5.0 that might change how we all use shared state in Vue 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shawn Wildermuth)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Cumulative Layout Shift (CLS) Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/how-to-fix-cumulative-layout-shift-issues/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s Core Web Vitals initiative has taken the SEO and Web Performance worlds by storm and many sites are busy optimizing their Page Experience to maximize the ranking factor. The Cumulative Layout Shift metric is causing trouble to a lot of sites, so let’s have a look at ways of addressing any issues for that metric.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of An Online Store (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/front-end-performance-online-store-jewellerybox/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a good performance score from Google is hard for any website — but doing so for an online store is even harder. We achieved green scores — even several for mobile. Here is how we did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jennifer Brehm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 38 With Ivan Akulov: Why Is My React App Slow?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/smashing-podcast-episode-38/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about React performance. What factors slow our React apps down, and how can we fix it? Drew McLellan talks to expert Ivan Akulov to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up A Currency Convertor With ExchangeRatesApi.io]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/06/currency-convertor-exchangeratesapi/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon allows visitors to display prices in their own currency. Thanks to *ExchangeRatesApi.io*, we can do the same for our online shops, providing a better experience to our customers. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy June Vibes For Your Screen (2021 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What could be a better way to welcome June than with some colorful inspiration? Well, we might have something for you: wallpapers created with love by artists and designers from across the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>