<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-05-14T01:11:08.338Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-14T01:11:08.338Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.6.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340490</id>
        <link href="https://chenhuijing.com/blog/devtools-for-css-layouts-2021-edition/#%F0%9F%9A%B2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T23:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Hui Jing covers some recent movement in DevTools:
Firefox’s grid inspector was pretty full-featured from the get-to and&#160;released together with CSS grid in Firefox 52. It was constantly improved upon since. Chrome added a&#160;basic grid inspector 
&#8230;
The post DevTools for CSS layouts 2021 edition appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340573</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/2021-design-systems-survey-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T22:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friends at Sparkbox are doing a survey on design systems, as they do each year. Go ahead and fill it out if you please. Here are the results from last year. In both 2019 and 2020, the vibe was &#8230;
The post 2021 Design Systems (Survey/Courses) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an Email Newsletter [2021 Tutorial] – Design, Layout, Send]]></title>
        <id>609414f32cd0545b5e943526</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-email-newsletter-design-layout-send/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T21:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you manage a large community, chances are you need a way to communicate updates to your members quickly and efficiently. An email newsletter can be a very effective way to do so. In this article, I am going to provide some tips and suggestions for maximizing the impact and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Software Testing? The 10 Most Common Types of Tests Developers Use in Projects]]></title>
        <id>609952396008950828b3ea8d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/types-of-software-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T19:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development and testing go hand in hand. And in the era of agile software development, with quick releases of small iterations, you should do testing more and more frequently.  In order to perform effective testing, you need to know about the different types of testing and when you should]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React Tutorial – How to Work with Multiple Checkboxes]]></title>
        <id>609bcc6a62ab9107fe5a9f08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-multiple-checkboxes-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T18:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Handling multiple checkboxes in React is completely different from how you use regular HTML checkboxes. So in this article, we'll see how to work with multiple checkboxes in React. You will learn: How to use a checkbox as a Controlled Input in ReactHow to use the array map and reduce]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Lawyer to Engineer at Google – How to Switch Careers and Learn New Skills]]></title>
        <id>609ccb0d62ab9107fe5aa0ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-lawyer-to-google-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a corporate lawyer for 12 years. I never thought I'd be working at Google as a software engineer, but now I am. And I'm going to share with you ten important lessons I learned during this career transition. I finished law school in Bangalore, India, a year before]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340036</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/advanced-css-animation-using-cubic-bezier/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with complex CSS animations, there is a tendency to create expansive @keyframes with lots of declarations. There are a couple of tricks though that I want to talk about that might help make things easier, while staying in &#8230;
The post Advanced CSS Animation Using cubic-bezier() appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svgator-3-0-reshapes-the-way-you-create-and-animate-svg-with-extensive-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T14:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building animations can get complicated, particularly compelling animations where you aren&#8217;t just rolling a ball across the screen, but building a scene where many things are moving and changing in concert. When compelling animation is the goal, a timeline GUI &#8230;
The post SVGator 3.0 Reshapes the Way You Create and Animate SVG With Extensive New Features appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Features of Angular’s Ivy Language Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/new-features-angular-ivy-language-service</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/new-features-angular-ivy-language-service"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T13:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a look at what Angular has officially released with Ivy Language Service, from type checking and error detection to platform consistency and codebase diagnosis.
You might have read our introduction to Angular Language Service post, where we gave you a look at experimental Ivy and what it&rsquo;s promising. Now Angular has officially released Ivy Language Service, and we are going to take a closer look at the incredible features it offers.
What Is Ivy Language Service?
Whenever you use an integrated dev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 13, 2021 (#3442)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33827</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/L-zz-SCd6HU/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T11:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Angular v12 is now available (Mark Techson) Windows Community Toolkit &#8211; Release v7.0.2 (Michael Hawker) AngularDart, Flutter, and the web: Spring update (Tim Sneath) My Favorite C# Features &#8211; Part 4: Project Structure (Jeffrey T. Fritz) Introducing the brand-new MvvmGen Library – Writing ViewModels for your XAML Applications Has Never Been More Productive [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3230]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7484</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/uz1HlD4Dfok/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software Visual Studio 2019 version 16.9 Release Notes &#8211; Visual Studio Team Information My Favorite C# Features &#8211; Part 4: Project Structure &#8211; Jeffrey T. Fritz ASP.NET Core in .NET 6 &#8211; Part 08 &#8211; CSS isolation for MVC Views and Razor Pages &#8211; Jürgen Gutsch Develop production-scale modern web apps quickly with Azure Static [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build and Deploy a Portfolio with Vue.js Axios, the GitHub REST API, and Netlify]]></title>
        <id>5fde208ae6787e09839407c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-portfolio-with-vuejs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T20:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this free book, we will build two simple projects and deploy them on Netlify. We will use Vue.js as our front-end framework, and use different technologies to build our projects.  If you follow this tutorial to the end, you will build a simplified version of Twitter and a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use the Kivy Python Library to Create Games and Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>609c215862ab9107fe5a9fa9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-the-kivy-python-library-to-create-games-and-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T18:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kivy is a free and open source Python framework for developing mobile apps and games with a natural user interface. We just released a 5-hour Kivy course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. In this Kivy course, you will learn to create games and applications with Python for every platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Telerik UI for ASP.NET AJAX R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-ajax-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-ajax-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We&rsquo;re excited to share more about our updates to Telerik UI for ASP.NET AJAX in our most recent release.
Hey developer folks, it&rsquo;s time for another release with new UI components, features and tooling for your ASP.NET AJAX applications. The Telerik R2 2021 release brings new Switch component, multiple Gantt enhancements such as Planned vs Actual, support for multiple templates for custom content rendering, online technical training available for both active trials and license holders and more.
R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Kendo UI for Angular with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-angular-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-angular-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for Angular is here.
With this release, we officially cross the 100 UI component threshold while introducing some highly requested features and UI components that are sure to please any Angular developer out there. Without further ado, let&rsquo;s jump straight into the latest and greatest in Angular with R2 2021.
Kendo UI for Angular Turns 100!

While we normally may measure how old something is by years, with a UI component library I prefer to measure by total number of com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Kendo UI for jQuery with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-jquery-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-jquery-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for jQuery is here. With this release comes the new TaskBoard, Skeleton and ActionSheet components, along with a ton of new features and improvements across existing components.
It&rsquo;s May and you know what that means&mdash;another huge update from Kendo UI for jQuery. With R2 2021 we have added some pretty nifty new components, including the new TaskBoard component, and other highly requested features, so let&rsquo;s get right to it and cover what&rsquo;s new in the jQue…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WinForms R2 2021: New Callout Control, Color Variations for Office2019 Theme and Content Controls in RichTextEditor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/winforms-r2-2021-new-callout-control-color-variations-office2019-theme-content-controls-richtexteditor</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/winforms-r2-2021-new-callout-control-color-variations-office2019-theme-content-controls-richtexteditor"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second official release of 2021 is here for the Telerik UI for WinForms suite. Enjoy the variety of new controls and improvements coming in R2 2021.
We are thrilled to announce the new Callout control, dark and gray versions of the Office2019 theme, content controls in RadRichTextEditor, Swiss QR barcode, Toast notifications for .NET 5 and much more. Since customer satisfaction has always been our top priority, 70+ customer-requested issues have also been addressed.
Let&rsquo;s dive into the sea of new …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Kendo UI for Vue with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-vue-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendo-ui-vue-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for Vue is here, bringing six new native UI components for Vue, including the Button, Floating Action Button and Upload components.
The R2 2021 release of Kendo UI for Vue is here and with it comes a big list of new native UI components for Vue. Let&rsquo;s dive straight in to see what&rsquo;s new in Kendo UI for Vue with R2 2021.
New Components
New Component: Button

Every application needs a button at some point&mdash;it&rsquo;s the main way we get users to perform an actio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in KendoReact with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendoreact-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-kendoreact-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[R2 2021 means: TypeScript and hook-equivalent support for our samples and demos, new components like Skeleton and Circular Gauge, and a slew of improvements across several existing components like the Data Grid and Gantt.
May is here and that means another exciting release of KendoReact. R2 2021 brings new components like the Circular Gauge and some highly requested features across a huge set of our existing UI components. Let&rsquo;s not drag things out and just jump straight into what&rsquo;s new in Kendo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik UI for WPF R2 2021 Brings Suggested Actions, New Barcodes, Dark Themes and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-wpf-r2-2021-brings-suggested-actions-new-barcodes-dark-themes-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-wpf-r2-2021-brings-suggested-actions-new-barcodes-dark-themes-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second major release for this year is live today. Announcing R2 2021 of Telerik UI for WPF and Telerik UI for Silverlight. 
R2 2021 is packed with cool stuff like: Suggested Actions and .NET 6 Preview 3 support, new Barcode implementation that brings few new Barcode types, official CardView, RichTextBox Shapes, many Document Processing features and lots more. On the top of all the features, we are adding dark variations for Material and VisualStudio2019 themes and introducing .NET 5 sample applications.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Telerik UI for ASP.NET MVC R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-mvc-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-mvc-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Telerik R2 2021 release brings new sleek and feature-rich components, plus big new features to some of your favorite components.
Hey developer folks, it&rsquo;s time for another massive release with new ASP.NET MVC UI components, features and tooling for your applications. 
The Telerik R2 2021 release brings sleek and feature rich MVC components such as Task Board, Circular Gauge, Action Sheet and Skeleton , plus new features in the Grid, Editor, Drawer, TreeList, QR Code, Scheduler and Map components, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Telerik UI for ASP.NET Core R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-core-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-aspnet-core-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Telerik R2 2021 release for UI for ASP.NET Core brings sleek and feature-rich components, plus new Grid, Editor features, Linux Installer, compatibility with .NET 6 latest preview and much more.
Hey developer folks, it&rsquo;s time for another massive release with new UI components, features and tooling for your ASP.NET Core applications.
The Telerik R2 2021 release brings sleek and feature-rich UI for ASP.NET Core Task Board, Circular Gauge, ActionSheet, Skeleton components plus new Grid, Editor featur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik UI for WinUI R2 2021: Scheduler, ListView, Latest Project Reunion Support and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-winui-r2-2021-scheduler-listview-latest-project-reunion-support-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-winui-r2-2021-scheduler-listview-latest-project-reunion-support-more"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our latest WinUI release is live now&mdash;announcing Telerik UI for WinUI R2 2021.
Telerik UI for WinUI R2 2021 is fully packed with fresh new components and features for your WinUI apps. Some of the new goodies are Scheduler, ListView, Shadow, RangeSlider, Swiss QR Barcode as well as many Document Processing features. In addition to all that, we are introducing Project Reunion 0.5.6 support and new sample app&mdash;WinUI Theme Editor.
Let&rsquo;s see what is new this release.
Project Reunion 0.5.6 Support…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik UI for Xamarin R2 2021: New Badge and Shadow Controls, PdfViewer Features and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-xamarin-r2-2021-new-badge-shadow-controls-pdfviewer-features-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/telerik-ui-for-xamarin-r2-2021-new-badge-shadow-controls-pdfviewer-features-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second major release of 2021 for Telerik UI for Xamarin for is here, and it&rsquo;s packed with exciting new components and improvements for you to enjoy.
We understand UI design is a highly important part of every mobile app, and our brand new Badge and Shadow components can help you achieve appealing designs. We&rsquo;ve also enhanced our Barcode control with the newest Swiss QR symbology and improved font support for the PdfViewer control. Read on for more details.
Badge
Badges are those small notifi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Telerik UI for Blazor R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-blazor-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-ui-blazor-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik UI for Blazor 2.24 release brings new PanelBar and Card components, Grid and TreeList updates, Blazor Reporting demo integration, Calendar templates, a new Visual Studio Code Converter Wizard and much more!
Hey developer folks, it&rsquo;s Telerik R2 2021 release time and we&rsquo;re excited to announce that the Telerik UI for Blazor component suite reached a new milestone of 75+ truly native components.
While we have continuously shipped new components and features in the period of January to May 20…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New in Telerik Reporting and Telerik Report Server with R2 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-reporting-telerik-report-server-r2-2021</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/whats-new-telerik-reporting-telerik-report-server-r2-2021"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik Reporting R2 2021 brings Blazor Report Designer, support for .NET 6 latest preview and more. Telerik Report Server R2 2021 comes with enhanced Web Report Designer.
Mid-May is here, and the beautiful spring brings the next major version of Telerik&rsquo;s take on the Reporting components and tools.
In addition to Blazor Report Designer and support for .NET 6 latest preview, the second release for the year also brings new enhancements in the Web Report Designer and Swiss Barcode support. Reports will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JustMock R2 2021: Performance Improvement, Debug Window Shows New Info, Support for .NET 6 Preview 3 and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.telerik.com/blogs/justmock-r2-2021-performance-improvement-debug-window-dotnet-6-preview-3-and-more</id>
        <link href="https://www.telerik.com/blogs/justmock-r2-2021-performance-improvement-debug-window-dotnet-6-preview-3-and-more"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T15:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the R2 2021 release of our mocking framework, Telerik JustMock.
The R2 2021 release of our mocking framework, Telerik JustMock, includes performance improvements, Debug Window showing information about the arguments used in the arrangement, support for .NET 6 Preview 3 and improvements in the Visual Studio extension. Let&rsquo;s look at the details.
Enhanced Telerik JustMock Profiler for Even Faster Unit Test Execution
With the previous JustMock release R1 2021, we shipped a configuration to spee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Telerik Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339960</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/making-disabled-buttons-more-inclusive/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T14:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about disabled buttons. Specifically, let’s get into why we use them and how we can do better than the traditional disabled attribute in HTML (e.g. &#60;button disabled&#62; ) to mark a button as disabled.
There are lots of &#8230;
The post Making Disabled Buttons More Inclusive appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandrina Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating Design Patterns That Need Fixing: Birthday Picker]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/frustrating-design-patterns-birthday-picker/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this new series of articles on UX, we take a closer look at some frustrating design patterns and explore better alternatives, along with plenty of examples to keep in mind when building or designing one. Let’s start with an infamous birthday picker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 12, 2021 (#3441)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33825</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/HZQ2DujgUxo/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T11:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Manage Windows Package Manager with Group Policy (Demitrius Nelon) Supporting VB.NET in .NET 5 &#124; On .NET (Richard Lander, Klaus Loffelmann &#38; Merrie McGaw) Visual Studio 2019 version 16.9 Release Notes &#8211; version 16.9.5 new release (Microsoft Docs) Hosting Uno Platform WebAssembly apps on Azure Static Web Apps (Gerard Gallant) Web &#38; Cloud [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Little Smashing Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/little-smashing-stories/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the day we sent out our 300th edition of the Smashing Newsletter. This article is a little celebration in which we share little Smashing stories from people working behind the scenes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3229]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7482</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/EB8TKF1wzgM/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-12T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Put a DPAD on that GC! &#8211; Maoni Stephens .NET May 2021 Updates – 5.0.6, 3.1.15, 2.1.28 &#8211; Rahul Bhandari Building an Event Driven .NET Application: The Fundamentals &#8211; Paul DeVito Making the calculator thread-safe: Creating a Simple Moving Average calculator in C# &#8211; Part 2 &#8211; Andrew Lock Using C# Named Arguments to [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Selenium and Python to Scrape Websites More Effectively]]></title>
        <id>6096aafe2cd0545b5e944430</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-web-scraping-with-selenium/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're scraping data from the web with Python, Selenium will often come up as an helpful tool to use. It was originally designed for automated testing, but its scraping capabilities are impressive, too. This is because Selenium can do things that other libraries or frameworks often can't when collecting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340359</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-pie-timer-re-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kitty reflected on an ancient blog post here on CSS-Tricks on how to make an animated pie timer. The old technique is still clever. The new technique is equally clever and much easier. I particularly like the steps() animation function&#8230;
The post CSS Pie Timer Re-Revisited appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I could build this during the weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340186</id>
        <link href="https://world.hey.com/joaoqalves/i-could-build-this-during-the-weekend-aa093c5e"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T21:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many times have you heard that (or even uttered it under your own breath)? I know I&#8217;ve heard it in conversations. I also know I&#8217;ve wondered the same thing about a product or two — hey, the idea here &#8230;
The post I could build this during the weekend appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write a Résumé – Practical Guide with Example Résumé]]></title>
        <id>6093929601fc34080ef81a0f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-a-resume-with-example/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T19:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a résumé can be a little intimidating. And the pressure to make it really good and fill in each detail can be tiresome and scary. This is especially true if you're doing it for the first time, because you might not know what to add in or what to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Beautiful Page Transitions in Angular]]></title>
        <id>609a73156008950828b3f2ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beautiful-page-transitions-in-angular/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s world, just having a website is not enough. The website needs to have a clean UI and it needs to be intuitive. And most importantly, it needs to have some sort of interactive element. Interactivity keeps users glued to your site for longer periods of time. As]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get a Job by Building Relationships – Advice from a Senior Software Engineer]]></title>
        <id>609552842cd0545b5e943bcd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-a-job-by-building-relationships/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T17:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The job search is exhausting. You apply to countless jobs through LinkedIn and company websites. Apply, apply, apply. Submit, submit, submit. You're tired.  But you know that's not even the worst part. The worst part is the black hole your applications seem to fall into 95% of the time. Is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Gen CSS: @container]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/next-gen-css-container/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome is experimenting with @container, a property within the CSS Working Group Containment Level 3 spec being championed by Miriam Suzanne of Oddbird, and a group of engineers across the web platform. @container brings us the ability to &#8230;
The post Next Gen CSS: @container appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Una Kravets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340106</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/distributed-persistent-rendering-dpr/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T14:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Jamstack, Netlify is coining this term.
If your reaction is: great, a new thing I need to know about and learn, know that while Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) does involve some new things, this is actually a push &#8230;
The post Distributed Persistent Rendering (DPR) appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Primer On CSS Container Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/complete-guide-css-container-queries/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prototype of the long-awaited CSS container queries has landed in Chrome Canary and is available for experimentation. Let’s look at what problem is being solved, learn how container queries work, and see how they compare with and complement existing CSS features for layout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 11, 2021 (#3440)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33823</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/Cr1cWwAYepE/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T11:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Put a DPAD on that GC! (Maoni Stephens) String Manipulation in C#: Best Practices (Steve Gordon) Rust for Windows Achieves Full Consumption (Call any Windows API) (David Ramel) Visual Studio 2022 64 bits: Elements of history (Patrick Smacchia) Register for Microsoft BUILD 2021 this year! Here&#8217;s a SNEAK PEAK of the First MINUTE! [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conference Platform We Use For Our Online Events: Hopin]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashingconf-conference-platform-hopin/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2020, the SmashingConf team was ready for a new year. We had so many things that excited us. New speakers, new workshops, new cities, new attendees, new experiences. And as we all know, 2020 had other ideas. With so many people working from home, we thought we would bring our [Smashing workshops](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops/) from our home offices to yours &mdash; but how?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amanda Annandale)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3228]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7480</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/pe1z--o5Qb8/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-11T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Using C# Named Arguments to Declutter Complex Tests &#8211; Matthew Jones Present and Verify Verifiable Credentials in ASP.NET Core using Decentralized Identities and MATTR# &#8211; Damien Bowden 5 Ways to Improve the Performance of C# Code for Free &#8211; Sasha Mathews Introducing C# 10 &#8211; Ken Bonny Code Coverage &#38; Frontend Testing &#8211; Muhammad [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topframe]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340020</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/topframe/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is extremely fun. Jeff Lindsay has created Topframe, and writes:
Anybody that knows how to mess around with HTML can now mess around with their desktop computing experience.&#160;Topframe&#160;is an open source tool that lets you 
&#8230;
The post Topframe appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=340208</id>
        <link href="https://benfrain.com/migrating-from-parcel-to-snowpack-build-tool-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T21:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I find build tooling endlessly interesting, especially right now as we&#8217;re in a juicy next-gen transitional period with players like Vite, wmr, Snowpack, and esbuild. Hugh Haworth has a good run-down of the new players, and we&#8217;ve chatted on &#8230;
The post Migrating from Parcel to Snowpack appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339203</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/variable-aspect-ratio-card-with-conic-gradients-meeting-along-the-diagonal/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T14:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across an interesting problem. I had to implement a grid of cards with a variable (user-set) aspect ratio that was stored in a --ratio custom property. Boxes with a certain aspect ratio are a classic problem in &#8230;
The post Variable Aspect Ratio Card With Conic Gradients Meeting Along the Diagonal appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Tudor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 10, 2021 (#3439)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33821</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/fJ3DAx2xzL0/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links ASP.NET Core 6 and Authentication Servers (Barry Dorrans) How to create the Tic-Tac-Toe game in Blazor WebAssembly in one hour! (David Grace) C# Async Yield Return: IAsyncEnumerable will change your life!!! (Brian Lagunas) Merge Conflict 253: Past, Present, &#38; Future of Ooui (James Montemagno &#38; Frank Kreuger) Intro of DevOps Dojo (Kan Tang) [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Started With React By Building A Whac-A-Mole Game]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/get-started-whac-a-mole-react-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to get started with React but struggling to find a good place to start? This article should have you covered. We’ll focus on some of the main concepts of React and then we’ll be building a game from scratch!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3227]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7478</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/jactCA24YRs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information ASP.NET Core 6 and Authentication Servers &#8211; Barry Dorrans State-Of-The-Art Natural Language Processing in .NET on the Edge &#8211; Ian Bebbington C# Async Yield Return: IAsyncEnumerable will change your life!!! &#8211; Brian Lagunas Top 10 Free New Testing Tools for Visual Studio 2019 &#8211; David Ramel Add a README to Your NuGet Package &#8211; [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is CSS a Programming Language?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339781</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-css-a-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a real distaste for this question. It might seem like a fun question to dig into on the surface, but the way it enters public discourse rarely seems to be in good faith. There are ulterior motives at &#8230;
The post Is CSS a Programming Language? appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links on Typography]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339574</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/links-on-typography/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T13:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are a few great links about typography that have been burning a hole in my saved bookmarks folder that I'm just now getting around to sharing. There's good stuff in there, from how to choose typefaces for app design to ideas for how to fix the concept of font sizing in CSS.
The post Links on Typography appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 7, 2021 (#3438)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33819</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/1KXFcBgAfF8/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T11:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Creating beautiful dual-screen Xamarin.Forms apps (Craig Dunn) Announcing Rust for Windows v0.9 (Angela Zhang) Add a README to Your NuGet Package (Christopher Gill) Building Accessible Mobile Apps &#124; The Xamarin Show (James Montemagno &#38; Rachel Kang) Software Engineering Radio Episode 458: Daniel Roth on Blazor (Priyanka Raghavan) Web &#38; Cloud Development Azure Tips [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Organize Product-Related Assets And Collaborate Better]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/product-records-organization-collaboration-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you organize your Google Drive assets? How do you name your Dropbox Paper documents? How do you deal with comments? Let’s get it right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Valeriia Panina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Morning Brew #3226]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cwa.me.uk/?p=7475</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/ReflectivePerspective/~3/u4LZK25KeMg/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Information Visual Studio Code &#8211; April 2021 (version 1.56) &#8211; Visual Studio Code Team and Contributors Event Based Architecture: What do you mean by EVENT? &#8211; Derek Comartin Add a README to Your NuGet Package &#8211; Christopher Gill EF Core &#8211; Robert Green &#38; Jeremy Likness AgileMapper v1.8 Released &#8211; Steve Wilkes Postman I ❤️ [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Alcock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Email…]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=339822</id>
        <link href="https://www.caniemail.com/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T02:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I&#8217;m 85% certain you&#8217;ve seen and used Can I Use&#8230;, I bet there is only a 13% chance that you&#8217;ve seen and used Can I Email&#8230;. It&#8217;s the same vibe—detailed support information for web platform features—except instead &#8230;
The post Can I Email&#8230; appeared first on CSS-Tricks.
You can support CSS-Tricks by being an MVP Supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The Performance Of Shopify Themes (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/improving-performance-shopify-themes-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When dealing with themes for large platforms and CMS, legacy issues often become a bottleneck. In this article, Carson Shold discusses how his team improved the performance and organization of their Shopify themes, and improved maintainability along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carson Shold)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 5, 2021 (#3437)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33817</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/KIxVRsSxGJI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T11:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Getting Started with Azure Web PubSub Service (Abhijit Jana) Visual Studio Icon Visual Studio 2019 for Mac version 8.9 Release Notes (v8.9.8 Released) (Microsoft Docs) The Rise of Asynchronous Collaboration and What It Means for Development Teams (Drew Falkman &#38; Jay Garcia) How we use Web Components at GitHub (Kristján Oddsson) .NET Foundation [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing HTML Payload With Next.js (Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/reduce-data-sent-client-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-05T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article showcases a case study of Bookaway’s landing page performance. We’ll see how taking care of the props we send to Next.js pages can make loading times and Web Vitals better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Liran Cohen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Undoing Mistakes With Git]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/undoing-mistakes-git-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how experienced you are, mistakes are an inevitable part of software development. But we can learn to repair them! And this is what we'll be looking at in this two-part series: how to undo mistakes using Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tobias Günther)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May the 4th, 2021 (#3436)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33815</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/QgAmpMAdlhI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T11:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links The future of gRPC in C# belongs to grpc-dotnet (Jan Tattermusch) .NET Annotated &#124; May 2021 (Rachel Appel) Evolving modular monoliths: 1. An architecture for .NET (Jon P. Smith) Quickly develop apps with App Studio for Microsoft Teams (Office Dev Center) Web &#38; Cloud Development Lost in Azure cloud identity &#8211; part 2 [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 36 With Miriam Suzanne: What Is The Future Of CSS?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/smashing-podcast-episode-36/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re starting our new season of the Smashing Podcast with a look at the future of CSS. What new specs will be landing in browsers soon? Drew McLellan talks to expert Miriam Suzanne to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – May 3, 2021 (#3435)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33813</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/_p9OizUJxHI/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T11:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Azure Event Grid, Event Hubs, and Service Bus Library Improvements (Lily Ma) .NET Foundation March/April 2021 Update (Claire Novotny) Cloud Engineering: The Future Is Now (Sophia Parafina) Visual Designer, Hot Reload and Beyond (Nick Randolph) Web &#38; Cloud Development What&#8217;s new in Svelte: May 2021 (Daniel Sandoval) You Can Label a JavaScript `if` [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Evolution Of Jamstack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/05/evolution-jamstack/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web-oriented databases, frameworks like Nuxt and Next.js, and even frameworkless approaches are evolving the Jamstack, but the core principles are more powerful than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mathias Biilmann)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – April 30, 2021 (#3434)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33810</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/7kdyHC9dQVw/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T10:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Easily build real-time apps with WebSockets and Azure Web PubSub—now in preview (Balan Subramanian) Multi-tenancy with EF Core in Blazor Server Apps (Jeremy Likness) Announcing XD to Flutter v2.0! (Grant Skinner) Getting Started Calling the Microsoft Graph API (Dan Wahlin) Make microservices fun again with Dapr (Dave Brock) Web &#38; Cloud Development Access [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Is In The Air (2021 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new collection of wallpapers is for you. Designed with love by the community for the community, the wallpapers are available with and without a calendar for May 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble `<img>` Element And Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/humble-img-element-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images have also been a key part of the web. They communicate ideas instantly, but they are also a lot heavier than text to load. This means that it’s essential to get loading and displaying them right, if you want to give your users a fantastic first impression. An excerpt from [Addy's new book](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/) (also, check a [free PDF preview](http://provide.smashingmagazine.com/eBooks/image-optimization-sample-chapter.pdf)).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Addy Osmani)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – April 29, 2021 (#3433)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33808</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/yUtbF40z08I/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-29T10:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Running Your Windows UI / Project Reunion App in the Windows App Container (sandbox) (Nick Randolph) Learning Path: Microsoft Graph Fundamentals (Microsoft Learn) GitHub Desktop supports hiding whitespace, expanding diffs, and creating repository aliases (Billy Griffin) Beyond Calibri: Finding Microsoft’s next default font (Microsoft Design Team) Rearchitecting for Microservices: Featuring Windows &#38; Linux [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Image Optimization, A New Smashing Book By Addy Osmani]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/image-optimization-pre-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is out! For the last year, we’ve been working with Addy Osmani on a new Smashing Book all around image optimization. And now it’s here. Meet “Image Optimization”, our practical modern guide to delivering high-quality images on the web with the best performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – April 28, 2021 (#3432)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33805</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/jks23uQIQBM/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-28T11:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Uno Platform 3.7 – More WinUI, Project Reunion and Linux support, Wasm performance boost (Uno Platform Team) Help Plan the Next Phase of the Azure SDK (Azure SDK) Interactive C# with VS Code Notebooks with Eric Potter &#8211; Adventures in .NET 066 (Shawn Clabough &#38; Wai Liu) Microsoft Build 2021, A Free Digital [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Easing Functions For CSS Animations And Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/easing-functions-css-animations-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Easing functions can change the look and feel of an animation by affecting the rate, or speed, of an animation. In this article, we’re going to take a deep dive into easing functions and see how we can use them to create those natural and stunning animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dew Drop – April 27, 2021 (#3431)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alvinashcraft.com/?p=33803</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/alvinashcraft/~3/jOygmaRY01U/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-27T11:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top Links Announcing Viva Learning public preview (John Mighell) Update existing projects to the latest release of Project Reunion (Microsoft Docs) &#8211; v0.5.6 now available! Build and ship software better with GitHub and Microsoft Teams (Microsoft Teams Team) Introducing GraphQLinq &#8211; Strongly Typed GraphQL Queries with LINQ to GraphQL. (Giorgi Dalakishvili) Clean Architecture Refactoring: A [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alvin A.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Bake Layers Of Accessibility Testing Into Your Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/bake-layers-accessibility-testing-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility experts Kate Kalcevich and Mike Gifford introduce readers to "layered accessibility testing”, a practice of using a variety of tools and approaches at different stages in the digital product lifecycle to catch accessibility issues early &mdash; when it’s easier and cheaper to fix them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich &amp; Mike Gifford)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Newly Supported, Modern CSS Pseudo-Class Selectors]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/guide-supported-modern-css-pseudo-class-selectors/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CSS Working Group Editor’s Draft for [Selectors Level 4](https://drafts.csswg.org/selectors-4/) includes several pseudo-class selectors that already have proposal candidates in most modern browsers. This guide will cover ones that currently have the best support along with examples to demonstrate how you can start using them today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: The Ordinary Made Extraordinary (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-done-well-part1/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s the little things in web life that make us look twice. From carousels to documentation to cookie disclaimers, here are some sites taking the mundane and sprinkling in a little magic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/incremental-static-regeneration-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR) is a new evolution of the Jamstack, allowing you to update static content instantly without needing a full rebuild of your site. The hybrid approach of Next.js allows you to use ISR for e-commerce, marketing pages, blog posts, ad-backed media, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lee Robinson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Content Is Such A Fundamental Part Of The Web Design Process]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/content-fundamental-part-web-design-process/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-21T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As designers, we are often burdened by the responsibility of producing and managing website content. It’s not our job to write it, but it’s not the client’s either. We can avert disaster by including content production in the design process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Saunders)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making GraphQL Work In WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/making-graphql-work-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-20T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore the plugins providing GraphQL servers to WordPress. When should we use WPGraphQL, and when the GraphQL API for WordPress? Is there some advantage of one over the other, or some particular task that is easier to accomplish with one of them? In this article, we will find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An In-Depth Guide To Measuring Core Web Vitals]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/complete-guide-measure-core-web-vitals/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-19T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How are Core Web Vitals measured? How do you know your fixes have had the desired effect and when will you see the results in Google Search Console? Let’s figure it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Mistakes To Avoid In Your Technical Interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/mistakes-technical-interviews/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/mistakes-technical-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that the technical interview process leaves something to be desired; it’s often riddled with anxiety and stress. In this article, we’ll take a look at seven of the most common mistakes candidates make in their technical interviews and explore ways you can avoid them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Emma Bostian)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Web Design Clients Fast (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-clients-fast-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/web-design-clients-fast-part2/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Selling is key to growing your web design business, but it doesn’t have to be complicated! With clear goals, customer research, and proven closing techniques, anyone can find new clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephen Roe)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cats With Love: New Navigation, Guides And Workshops]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/from-cats-with-love-navigation-guides-workshops/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/04/from-cats-with-love-navigation-guides-workshops/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Smashing, we’ve been busy over the last few months. We’ve set up new workshops, redesigned our navigation, refined performance and improved accessibility. There are subtle UX changes coming in, and we’d love to share what we’ve been cooking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>